[{"id":"100","question":"user message","answer":"generated response"},{"id":"101","question":" Net Asset Value (NAV) of the mutual fund.","answer":"Mutual fund serves as a suitable option for investors looking to get high return on their investments. Mutual fund, a high-risk, high-return proposition, is invested in various equity and debt instruments. Equity mutual fund primarily invest in stocks. Mutual fund stocks are classified according to the portfolio holdings. While, debt mutual fund schemes disperse the money in fixed income instruments such as bonds, government securities, corporate debentures, money market instruments, etc. This was all about the basic details of mutual fund. Now, get down to the Net Asset Value (NAV) of the mutual fund.\n\nNAV, which is the price at which the mutual fund units are purchased or sold, arrives after deducting the liabilities. The value of all units is calculated daily after subtracting all the expenses. Subsequently, the value gets divided by the total number of units to arrive at the NAV, which is also known as Net Book Value or Book Value."},{"id":"102","question":" Public Provident Fund (PPF)","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/compare-elss-and-other-tax-saving-schemes/"},{"id":"103","question":"(Past performance of the sponsor) PPFAS Mutual Fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/ppfas-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"104","question":"[Car Loan]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/wish-car"},{"id":"105","question":"[Car]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/car-loan"},{"id":"106","question":"[Car]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/car-loan"},{"id":"107","question":"[Child's Future Loan]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/wish-child"},{"id":"108","question":"[Home Loan]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/wish-home"},{"id":"109","question":"[Home]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loan"},{"id":"110","question":"[Home]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loan"},{"id":"111","question":"[No]","answer":"Ooppss!! No Problem."},{"id":"112","question":"[Personal]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loan"},{"id":"113","question":"[Personal]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loan"},{"id":"114","question":"[Travelling Loan]","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/wish-travel"},{"id":"115","question":"[Yes]","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"116","question":"10 Useful Tricks to Get the Best Home Loan Offer","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/10-useful-tricks-to-get-the-best-home-loan-offer/"},{"id":"117","question":"5 Easy Tips to Get Off from CIBIL Defaulter’s List While Availing a Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/5-easy-tips-get-off-cibil-defaulters-list-availing-personal-loan/"},{"id":"118","question":"5 Unexpected Reasons for Your Personal Loan Rejection","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/unexpected-reasons-for-personal-loan-rejection/"},{"id":"119","question":"a good tool to grow and safeguard your investment","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/balanced-funds-good-tool-grow-safeguard-investment/"},{"id":"120","question":"A tool for uninterrupted growth of MF portfolio","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/sip-pause-option-tool-uninterrupted-growth-mf-portfolio/"},{"id":"121","question":"advantages Debt Mutual Funds","answer":"Returns Better Than Competing Products – Debt mutual fund investments can help generate returns around 8%-9% in the short-term, faring better than its competing product i.e. fixed deposit wherein the anticipated returns would be around 7%.\n\nIndexation Benefits – Indexation benefits are applicable to debt funds when you sell the units after 3 years of holding them. Capital gains arising from the sale would be taxed at 20% with the benefit of indexation, which is a tool that takes into account the inflation prevailing between the period when you bought the MF units and the period when you sell the same. This inflates the purchase price to reduce the capital gains so that the tax liability lowers down considerably than otherwise."},{"id":"122","question":"Advantages of a Home Loan Top-Up Over a Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/advantages-of-a-home-loan-top-up-over-a-personal-loan/"},{"id":"123","question":"Advantages of Balance Fund","answer":"        With balanced fund, you get higher returns from equity and the stability factor of debt\n        Returns from balanced funds can be risk-adjusted if asset allocation is efficiently done by the fund manager. Choosing mid cap and small cap stocks for investment can offer higher returns, which will get safeguarded by the stable flow of income from debt instrument.\n        If you have set yourself to invest in balanced fund, which is equity focussed, for a long-term, then you can receive capital gain tax exemption on majority of the investment as well as indexation benefit of debt component for holding the investments above a year. "},{"id":"124","question":"Advantages of gilt fund","answer":"        The biggest advantage is that you can invest in government securities through gilt funds at Rs 5,000. The minimum limit for investment government securities stands at Rs 5 crores.\n        Gilt funds invest across different government securities offering varying returns when you route the investment through fund managers. So, the diversification element is taken care of and you get good returns."},{"id":"125","question":"Advantages of Gold ETF investment","answer":"        Seamless trading on stock exchange\n        Easy and quick transaction through demat account\n        Transparent pricing\n        You can hold the asset via electronic form"},{"id":"126","question":"Agriculture Loan","answer":"Those individuals engaged in the agriculture sector, this scheme is very useful for them. Under this scheme, the government has collaborated with many banks and financial institutions to give agriculture loans to unemployed youth in the country. People who can apply under this scheme should be aged 22 or above."},{"id":"127","question":"Am I eligible to get loan ?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"128","question":"Am I eligible to get loan from Wishfin ?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"129","question":"An Overview on Taking Personal Loan Against Gold","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/overview-taking-personal-loan-gold/"},{"id":"130","question":"Are You a Business Traveller? Checkout These Credit Cards","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/credit-card/business-traveller-checkout-credit-cards/"},{"id":"131","question":"Are You Personal Loan Ready?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/are-you-personal-loan-ready/"},{"id":"132","question":"Avoid reckless spending to reap benefits of higher credit limit on credit card","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/credit-card/avoid-reckless-spending-reap-benefits-higher-credit-limit-credit-card/"},{"id":"133","question":"Axis Bank Smart Traveller Credit Card","answer":"Get a card that comes with extra travel benefits to make your journeys rewarding\n\nAnnual Fee: ₹250 (Can get waived on a spend of ₹2,500 within 45 days)\n\nPrivileges & Perks\n\n        8 points on every ₹200 spent on the credit card while traveling abroad\n        4 points for ever ₹200 spent on hotels, holiday packages, airlines, train and bus bookings in India\n        2 points on every ₹200 spent on the credit card in India\n        1% fuel surcharge waiver on all fuel transactions in India with an Axis Bank Titanium Credit Card\n        Valid on transactions between ₹400 and ₹4,000 only\n        Maximum benefits up to ₹400* per month\n        Get 15% discount on dining at partner restaurants in India"},{"id":"134","question":"Balanced Funds (Hybrid Funds)","answer":"A type of fund that offers a mixture of safety, income and modest capital appreciation. This investment option owns both stocks and bonds and is an option for intermediate-term investors to invest. The asset allocation may vary as per market conditions.\n\n        Want to enjoy the benefits of both the worlds, i.e. equity and debt? If yes, say hello to balanced funds, giving you both capital appreciation and income generation.\n        These types of funds invest in a mix of both equity and debt instruments in the proportion decided by the fund managers after studying the market conditions.\n        Balanced funds generate high income from equity while the regular flow of money is ensured via investments made in debt instruments.\n"},{"id":"135","question":"Balanced funds (Hybrid Funds)","answer":"Hunting for a mutual fund that can not only grow your money but also safeguard it? Then, your search ends with balanced funds that invest your money in equity and debt instruments in good proportion. As a result, these funds are able to lower the risk and increase the returns of investors. Equity funds are called high-risk, high-return proposition, while debt counterparts offer you stable return. But, balanced funds aim to provide more returns and reduce the risk as well.The risk element simply goes away in the long-term. So, it offers a perfect mean  for investors to park their hard earned money.\n"},{"id":"136","question":"Banks, Where To Get A Personal Loan?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/where-to-get-a-personal-loan/"},{"id":"137","question":"Be Cautious/ Considerations while Investing in NFOs","answer":"NFOs come with a higher degree of risks. So, you need to be vigilant and take necessary measures as stated below.\n\n1. Absence of Proven Track Record\n\nNFOs debut with a new idea, investment theme or sector and thus it becomes increasingly difficult to estimate the performance of the fund in the future. You can always take a call on the old funds by checking their performance over the years. However, the same is not possible in case of NFO due to the lack of a proven track record.\n\n2. High Initial Expenses\n\nWith NFOs, come the higher marketing charges and other initial expenses, which form a certain percentage of the assets being held by the fund. These expenses are deducted from the net asset value (NAV) and thus shrink the returns substantially. So, when you look to buy new funds, make sure the charges are not high.\n\n3. NFOs Not Cheaper than Other Funds\n\nDon’t go by the illusion that NFOs, which are generally offered at Rs 10 per unit, are cheaper than other funds with NAV of more than Rs 10. As soon as the NFO period gets over, AMCs will invest the money, accumulated in the fund, in the underlying assets and the sum of investment value of all the securities on any given day will thus become the new price of the NFO.\n\n4. Reduced Scope for Diversification\n\nNFOs are usually sector specific and focus on certain mid cap or small cap funds, thereby resulting in reduced diversification of your investments. Proper diversification plays a vital role in strengthening the mutual fund portfolio by compensating the investors for the loss in one sector with the returns made in other.\n\n5. Read the Investment Objective Carefully\n\nIt becomes important to carefully read the investment objective of the NFO before investing in the same. With the objective, you can make out whether the NFO will help you achieve your investment goals or not. Suppose your goal is to create a large corpus to invest in the wedding of your children 20 years later, then the objective of NFO should read as capital appreciation over the long-term. If the objective does not match your needs, then stay away from investing in the NFO."},{"id":"138","question":"Benefits of investing in Mutual Fund SIP","answer":"Have a look at the benefits of investing in SIP:\n\n        Systematic Investment Plan (SIP)- As the name suggests, you can do the investment in a disciplined and systematic way for a chosen time period\n        You can start the investment with the minimum amount of ₹500\n        There is no TDS (Tax Deduction at Source) on Debt funds\n        You get returns in the form of capital gain and dividends"},{"id":"139","question":"Benefits of SIP (Systematic Investment Plan)","answer":"        SIP is pocket-friendly as it allows you to make smaller amount of investment every month rather than a lump sum at one go\n        SIP offers you the advantage of rupee-cost averaging concept as it enables you to purchase more units with the downturn in the market and lesser units when the market is going up\n        SIP offers a convenient medium of investment as you are required just to fill up the enrolment form, submit it along with a cheque deposited on the date sought by the mutual fund. Subsequently, you will get units and a notification for the same will be sent to you. "},{"id":"140","question":"Benefits of SIP in Pre-Elections","answer":"Many experts believe that investing 6-8 months before the general election year can give you considerable returns. However, this is keeping the fact in mind that SIPs are best when held for long-term. Hence, if you are investing your money or you already have, then keep it in SIP for at least 2 years.\n\nIn the year 2009, we all know the market position improved and investors earned even up to 50% gains around election time. At that time, the other factors were also in the favor. Comparing the position of the market in previous years such as 1998, 2004, 2009, and 2014, there is no prominent trend. But, investing pre-election holds high chances of you receiving great returns.\n\nSo, if you are planning to invest in the SIPs, now would be the right time for it."},{"id":"141","question":"Best Air Miles Credit Cards in India","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-air-miles-credit-cards-india/"},{"id":"142","question":"Best Credit Cards for Online Shopping Discounts","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-for-online-shopping/"},{"id":"143","question":"Best Credit Cards for Students with No/Bad Credit History","answer":"These days, many credit card companies have started offering the best credit cards for students also. Yes, now students can also avail the credit cards by following an easy and simple procedure. In fact, those who are having bad or no credit history can also avail these cards with the help of issuers. Yes, there are many credit card providers available in the market that allow you to avail the card even if you are having low or bad credit history. In fact, they work for such types of applicants only, and ensure that they can avail the card instead of all the odds. So, if you are a student who is having no or bad credit history, nothing to worry, you can avail the credit cards of different banks with the help of these providers.\n\nSo I hope the next time someone asks you -What are the best credit cards for students in India, you will have the answer on your tips. And yes if you wish to avail the services of a credit card, talk to your parents and choose the one which suits you the best."},{"id":"144","question":"Best Credit Cards for this Diwali Season","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-for-festive-season/"},{"id":"145","question":"Best Credit Cards in India ","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-in-india-apply-online/"},{"id":"146","question":"Best Credit Cards to Have While Traveling Abroad","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-for-international-travel-abroad/"},{"id":"147","question":"Best Fuel Credit Cards You’d Love to Have While Driving","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-fuel-credit-cards-india/"},{"id":"148","question":"Best Mutual funds for retired people","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/best-mutual-funds-retired-people/"},{"id":"149","question":"Bond Fund","answer":"It is a type of debt fund that invests in bonds or other debt securities. These types of funds pay periodic dividends that include interest payments on the fund’s underlying securities along with periodic realized capital appreciation.\n\n        Created to manage an investment portfolio of individual bonds.\n        Investors purchase shares in the fund.\n        Each share represents the proportional ownership interest in the pool of bonds comprising the fund’s portfolio."},{"id":"150","question":"Calculate Returns on Your Mutual Fund Investment?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/calculate-returns-mutual-fund-investment/"},{"id":"151","question":"Can i afford taking loan?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"152","question":"Can I borrow some money?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"153","question":"Can I Get a Home Loan Without a Deposit?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/is-home-loan-without-deposit-possible/"},{"id":"154","question":"Can I get Loan from wishfin?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"155","question":"Can I get Loan?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"156","question":"Can you lend me loan?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"157","question":"Can you lend me some money?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"158","question":"capital protection debt funds (CPOS)","answer":"Capital protection-oriented scheme, a type of mutual fund scheme, which looks to protect at least the initial capital as well as give you the opportunity to make extra gains. These schemes are closed-ended funds that normally invest a majority of your money in highly secured debt instruments such as AAA-rated bonds and the remaining amount goes into the volatile segment, equity, which offers potential for higher returns. The scheme is oriented mainly toward the protection of the principal amount. At the end of the stipulated maturity period, the debt portion of the scheme grows to provide you the principal amount and the potential returns are offered by the equity portion. The principal amount here gets protected despite the fall in equity market. There is no guarantee that the capital will be protected but probabilities of capital safety is higher in this option."},{"id":"159","question":"Capital Protection Fund","answer":"It is a closed-ended scheme where no redemption is allowed before the maturity. The main objective of this fund is capital protection by investing in fixed income securities in line with the tenure seeking capital appreciation by investing in equity and equity-related instruments.\n\n        The portfolio comprises heavenly oriented towards debt and only a small portion is invested in equity.\n        These funds mainly invest in bonds, T-bills, Certificates of Deposits(CDs).\n        Since it is a closed-ended scheme, the fresh units can be availed during the new fund offer period (NFO).\n        The maturity of the debt portfolio is aligned with the lock-in period of the fund, thereby insulating it from the gyrations of interest rate movements."},{"id":"160","question":"Cash Loans","answer":"It is also a State-funded initiative that has been started by the Government of West Bengal. Under this scheme, an employed person aged between 18-45 can apply for a loan of up to Rs.50,000."},{"id":"161","question":"Categories of Loan provided by wishfin.","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"162","question":"Categories of Loan?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"163","question":"Charges that you must know before investing in mutual fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/charges-must-know-investing-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"164","question":"Check out the return and investment details of Franklin India Opportunities Fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/check-return-investment-details-franklin-india-opportunities-fund/"},{"id":"165","question":"Choose bond fund of your risk profile to avoid loss of money","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/choose-bond-fund-risk-profile-avoid-loss-money/"},{"id":"166","question":"Choose these financial instruments to begin your mutual fund journey","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/choose-financial-instruments-begin-mutual-fund-journey/"},{"id":"167","question":"CIBIL Score","answer":"CIBIL score or credit score is a numeric representation of the repayment history. When you apply for any credit facility (loans or credit cards) the lender checks your CIBIL score and your credit history. On the basis of the score and the credit hisory, your application is further processed. As CIBIL’s first official partner, Wishfin gives you the opportunity to check your CIBIL/Credit score for free by PAN card! You may now learn - how is CIBIL score generated and how can you check it online."},{"id":"168","question":"Citibank Cashback Credit Card","answer":"Now paying your bills has never been so rewarding as it is with Citibank Cashback credit card.\n\nAnnual Fee: ₹500\n\nPrivileges & Perks\n\n        For purchases up to ₹2,000 pay without entering the pin at the merchant terminals\n        5% cashback on all movie ticket purchases, subject to a maximum cap of ₹100 per month\n        5% cashback on all utility bill payments paid through Citibank online bill pay\n        5% cashback on all telephone bill payments\n        0.5% cash back on all other spends\n        Up to 15% savings across participating restaurants\n        Simple redemption policy\n        Get redemption in multiple of ₹500\n        Get your cash back conveniently and automatically as a statement credit\n        Multiple repayment options"},{"id":"169","question":"Classification of loan provided by wishfin.","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"170","question":"Classification of Loan.","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"171","question":"Comparing Tax-saving Products Available Under Section 80C on Different Investment Aspects","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/compare-elss-and-other-tax-saving-schemes/"},{"id":"172","question":"Comparison of Different Investment Options","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/lump-sum-bonus-investment/"},{"id":"173","question":"Comparition between Credit card and Personal loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/credit-card/credit-card-vs-personal-loan/"},{"id":"174","question":"Compounding","answer":"Guessing the right option was a bit tricky because the amount accumulated till day 15 was just Rs.16,384/- and most of the accumulation happened in the next 15 days. This is called the POWER OF COMPOUNDING, rightly called the 8th wonder of the world by none other than Albert Einstein, the Nobel winning scientist. Power of compounding works on 3 aspects – how much you invest, for how long you invest and the returns you expect."},{"id":"175","question":"Construction-linked plans","answer":"Here, you are supposed to make the payment in different phases. For example, the builder ask you to make minimum 10% to 15% booking amount, then next 10% or 12% of amount is required to deposit at the time they start construction and remaining money they charge in phases once they complete different floors. This is an easy way of payment and has many advantages of choosing the under-construction property."},{"id":"176","question":"Continue Your SIPs Even with Falling NAVs","answer":"If the market starts to drop, don’t panic or withdraw your SIP immediately. If you have placed your money in a stock with stable fundamentals and performance in relevance to other stocks, then you have no reason to worry.\n\nWhen you invest in SIPs regularly, you have the benefit of rupee-cost averaging. When the market is high, you buy lesser units and vice versa. This leads to good returns if you keep the SIP for long-term.\n\nIt is a common practice for investors to drop out when the market falls. But, you should keep investing fixed sum to receive rupee-cost averaging benefits."},{"id":"177","question":"Convert small investments into a big one with SIP mutual fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/convert-small-investments-big-one-sip/"},{"id":"178","question":"Credit card Vs. Personal loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/credit-card/credit-card-vs-personal-loan/"},{"id":"179","question":"Debt Funds","answer":"It is an investment tool which offers fixed income solutions while preserving your original investment. These types of funds are designed to invest in a mix of debt and fixed income securities by taking into account low-risk return investment avenue.\n\n        People with a lower risk appetite should go for debt funds. These funds are ideally suited for retirees seeking a regular flow of income.\n        The funds invest predominantly in government or corporate securities, bonds and other debt instruments.\n        Here investments can be short- term or long term, and the investors get the fixed returns at a lower risk to manage their daily expenses.\n        You can also avail the indexation benefits while selling your fund units after 3 years."},{"id":"180","question":"Debt Mutual Funds","answer":"Debt mutual funds are those funds that keep your money predominantly in fixed income instruments such as bonds, money-market instruments, etc."},{"id":"181","question":"Definition of Loan?","answer":"Loan is a thing that is borrowed, especially a sum of money that is expected to be paid back with interest. Do you want some? [yes,No]"},{"id":"182","question":"Difference between Credit card and Personal loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/credit-card/credit-card-vs-personal-loan/"},{"id":"183","question":"Disadvantage / pitfalls of gilt fund","answer":"        Gilt funds are not fully secured as the rise in interest rates bring a fall in the prices of government securities and thus adversely affect the performance of gilt funds you may have invested in.\n        Gilt funds are vulnerable to volatility risks with higher average maturity period of the fund\n        Gilt funds are liquid assets as they invest only in government securities that are not actively traded."},{"id":"184","question":"disadvantage or limitations of fixed deposits","answer":"Returns Not in Line with Inflation – The fixed deposits generate returns that are not in line with inflation. You can get an average return of around 6.50%-8.00% before tax. Post tax, the returns can come down to 5.50%. With such shoddy returns, you may find it hard to achieve your ambitious goals.\n\nLess Tax Efficient – The fixed deposit returns also come under the purview of the taxman. If you earn interest of more than ₹10,000 in a financial year, the Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) at 10% would be levied on the same.\n\nPremature Withdrawal Attracts Penalty – You could come across situations that would compel you to withdraw before the maturity. So, if you withdraw before your fixed deposit matures, you have to settle for a lesser proceed compared to when allowed to continue till the maturity. Premature withdrawal invites interest penalty of 1%-2%. So, if you deposit ₹1 lakh for 3 years, it would raise to ₹1,20,000 at maturity at 7% interest rate (assumed). If you withdraw after 2 years, the proceed would shorten to around ₹1,10,000."},{"id":"185","question":"Disadvantages of capital protection debt funds (CPOS)","answer":"        Capital protection funds are listed on the stock exchange as they are close-ended schemes. As a result, there are less chances that you can exit at fair value as liquidity on products listed on the exchanges has proved to be quite poor.\n        Long-term capital gain on these funds are taxed at 10.3% and 20.6% without indexation and indexation, respectively. Indexation is a tool that adjusts the purchase price for inflation while calculating long-term capital gain tax."},{"id":"186","question":"disadvantages or limitations of investing in gold","answer":"Sale Value Won’t Include Making Charges – Many of us buy gold to make jewellery, which includes making charges as well as the tax. Going by the current rate, 10 gram of 22 Karat gold costs ₹31,100. To make jewellery, one has to pay making charges at 10%. Further,  you need to pay the Goods and Services Tax (GST) at 3% over the entire sum. If you do the calculation, the total sum comes as ₹35,236.30. But when you sell the jewellery, you would get the real value of gold, not including the making charges and taxes.\n\nLack of Steady Income – You don’t stand to benefit from simply holding gold as it does not provide regular returns. Only when you sell the gold do you earn something out of it.\n\nBanks Do Not Take Back Gold Coins & Bars Once Sold – Many buy gold coins and bars only to be at the losing end as banks do not accept these ornaments once they sell it to you.\n\nStorage Charges Add to the Holding Cost of Gold – Gold is a precious metal that you want to be safe and secure. And so, you open a locker in banks to deposit gold ornaments to ensure their safety. But banks debit annual maintenance charges on the locker service. So, when you sell the gold ornaments to jewellers, they won’t factor in the maintenance charges that you must have paid to banks every year."},{"id":"187","question":"Dispel five myths to boost your investment portfolio with mutual funds","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/dispel-five-myths-boost-investment-portfolio-mutual-funds/"},{"id":"188","question":"dividend yield funds","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/take-quick-look-dividend-yield-funds/"},{"id":"189","question":"Do you provide loan?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"190","question":"Documentation Required by students for Credit Cards","answer":"        PAN card (required by few companies)\n        Birth certificate\n        Residential address proof\n        Identity card of the college (undergraduate or postgraduate)\n        College enrolment proof\n        2 passport sized colored photographs"},{"id":"191","question":"Documentation Required for Loed Fincap Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/lord-fincap-personal-loan/"},{"id":"192","question":"Documentation Required for SBM (State Bank of Mysore) Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/sbm-personal-loan/"},{"id":"193","question":"Documentation Required for State Bank of Bikaner and Jaipur (SBBJ) Personal Loan ","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/state-bank-of-bikaner-and-jaipur-personal-loan/"},{"id":"194","question":"Documentation Required for State Bank of Patiala (SBP) Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/state-bank-of-patiala-personal-loan/"},{"id":"195","question":"Documentation Required for Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-limited-personal-loan/"},{"id":"196","question":"Documentation Required for Union Bank of India Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/union-bank-india-personal-loan/"},{"id":"197","question":"Documentation required to avail gold loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/overview-taking-personal-loan-gold/"},{"id":"198","question":"Documents Required for Tab Capital Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/tab-capital-personal-loan/"},{"id":"199","question":"Documents Required for Vintage Financial Solutions Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/vintage-financial-solutions-personal-loan/"},{"id":"200","question":"Does a Personal Loan improve Credit Score ?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/does-a-personal-loan-improve-credit-score/"},{"id":"201","question":"Double Indexation","answer":"In case of mutual fund, indexation benefit is available for investments held for at least a year. But since inflation for the financial year is taken into account, so if you invest for over a year and it extends to three financial years, you stand to get the inflation benefit of two financial years. This is known as double indexation. The USP of double indexation is that you get the same even if you have invested for less than 2 years. Because, there are chances that your investment could come in the range of 3 financial years. If you had invested in March 2011 and redeemed the investment in April 2012, you will avail the double indexation benefit. Because, the investment had covered three financial years- FY 2010-11, FY 2011-12 and FY 2012-13. Fixed maturity plans offer double indexation benefit more than any other asset class as they have a maturity period of slightly above a year."},{"id":"202","question":"Economy of Investment","answer":"The mutual fund investment is economical as you can join the asset class by paying an amount as low as ₹500 on a monthly basis with a Systematic Investment Plan (SIP). An SIP is a disciplined approach to investing in a mutual fund at periodic intervals-daily, weekly, fortnightly, monthly, quarterly, half-yearly or annually. You can also switch to a lump-sum, one-time investment option and systematically withdraw the money from the same. Also, you have the facility to transfer your portfolio from one fund to another by availing the option of STP, which stands for Systematic Transfer Plan."},{"id":"203","question":"Effect of Elections on SIP Returns","answer":"For a lot of investors, the Indian equity market has been quite unexpected. The September came with the bad news as there was an 11.5% drop in 50-share Nifty. Others who have invested in mutual funds through Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) are considering withdrawing their money as soon as possible.\n\nMoreover, with 2019 general elections approaching, everyone is having second thoughts about any money they have invested. So, to clear the fog, we have evaluated how SIPs perform during election years. Let’s have a clear look."},{"id":"204","question":"Eligibility Criteria for Credit Cards for Students","answer":"Well the minimum age limit required to get these student credit cards is 18 years. The students should fulfill this basic eligibility criteria to own these credit cards."},{"id":"205","question":"Eligibility Criteria for SBM (State Bank of Mysore) Personal Loan","answer":"To get a personal loan from SBM, you must comply with the below eligibility criteria\n\n        Age at least 21 years and less than 58 years\n        Income criteria (Net salary-₹6000 or more) subject to at least 2 years of employment for Self-employed professionals\n        Salaried individuals under state/central governments, public or private companies, and multinational companies"},{"id":"206","question":"Eligibility Criteria for SBT (State Bank of Travancore) Personal Loan","answer":"        Age at least 21 years and 3 years before the retirement date of the borrower\n        Applicant should be an existing customer of SBT\n        All permanent employees of Central/state govt. schools, Colleges, Universities recognized by UGC/Central/State/Quasi Government, PSUs, Defence Personnel\n        Applicant must have worked for a minimum 1-year period\n        All employees in Private Sector Companies whose salary account is maintained with us and with a minimum service experience of 3 years.\n        Minimum net take home income of ₹20,000 (Government Employees) and ₹10,000 (Corporates)"},{"id":"207","question":"Eligibility Criteria for State Bank of Bikaner and Jaipur (SBBJ) Personal Loan ","answer":"        The applicant should be a permanent employee of either a reputed PSU, government organization or a decent private company\n        The individual should have a minimum net monthly income of ₹9,000\n        Should be at least 21 years of age and less than 58 years"},{"id":"208","question":"Eligibility Criteria for Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited","answer":"        Permanent employees whose age is less than 54 years.\n        Employees of government departments, approved educational institutions, business houses or reputed corporates"},{"id":"209","question":"Eligibility Criteria for Union Bank of India Personal Loan","answer":"        \tThe minimum age limit should be 21 years and maximum should be below 58 years.\n        Applicant should be an existing customer of Union Bank\n        Applicant should be a resident of India\n        Customer should have a regular income and should be a salaried employee (Government service or a regular corporate job) "},{"id":"210","question":"Eligibility Criteria for Vintage Financial Solutions Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/vintage-financial-solutions-personal-loan/"},{"id":"211","question":"Eligibility Criteria of Lord Fincap Personal Loan","answer":"The candidate with a stable source of income and belonging to the below- mentioned category is eligible to avail a loan from the company:\n\n        Salaried Individuals\n        Business Owners\n        Partnership/  Pvt. Ltd. Company\n        Professionals"},{"id":"212","question":"Eligibility Criteria of State Bank of Patiala (SBP) Personal Loan","answer":"        Age between 21 years and 60 years\n        The individual applying for the loan should be an Indian resident\n        The individual should have a source of income i.e. Should be salaried or proof a regular source of income if self-employed"},{"id":"213","question":"Eligibility Criteria of Tab Capital Personal Loan","answer":"This loan product is designed to meet the personal and business requirement of the salaried and self- employed professionals like –  CA, CS, Doctors and others."},{"id":"214","question":"ELSS (Equity Linked Savings Scheme)\n","answer":"A type of equity fund that offers twin benefits of capital appreciation and tax exemption to the investors. These tax-saving funds invest a majority of their portfolio in the stock market. It is a disciplinary Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) starts from as low as ₹500, best known for giving long-term capital gains along with the tax benefits.\n\n        Want to reap the tax benefits under mutual funds? If yes, you should know about Equity Linked Savings Scheme (ELSS).\n        A type of equity linked investment that offers tax deductions from the annual gross income for upto  ₹ 1.5 Lakh in a financial year.\n        An investor can enjoy the tax benefits under Section 80C of the Income Tax Act.\n        The investments made in ELSS have a lock-in period of 3 years."},{"id":"215","question":"Equity Funds","answer":"An equity fund also known as stock fund is a type of investment tool that offers capital appreciation and growth. These funds invest principally in stock market and are categorized according to company size , investment style of holdings in the portfolio and geography. Ideally suited to the investors looking for higher returns for a longer period of time with having medium to high risk taking appetite.\n\n        Those who have long-term financial goals like child education or marriage to fulfill, equity funds are ideal for them as it gives a lot of years to build on the corpus.\n        These funds invest mainly in equity and equity related instruments.\n        Returns are higher and so are the risks involved due to the massive volatility of the stock prices.\n        These can be rewarding because the long-term capital gains are exempted from tax.\n        A marginal allocation in debt instruments also gives a regular flow of income."},{"id":"216","question":"Equity Mutual Funds","answer":"The money invested in equity mutual funds is put into the high return proposition of equities. To achieve the investment fruition you need to stay invested for a long period, preferably for more than 3 years."},{"id":"217","question":"Equity-linked Savings Scheme (ELSS)","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/compare-elss-and-other-tax-saving-schemes/"},{"id":"218","question":"Equity-linked Savings Scheme (ELSS)","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/elss-perfect-investment-for-future/"},{"id":"219","question":"Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs)","answer":"An ETF is a bouquet of stocks, an investment fund traded on stock exchange. They are essentially index funds reflecting the composition of an Index like S&P CNX Nifty or BSE Sensex.\n\n        ETFs enable investors to get the broader exposure of the stock market in different countries and specific sectors.\n        The trading value is based on the net asset value of the underlying stocks that it represents.\n        You can buy and sell it in a real-time at a price that changes throughout the day."},{"id":"220","question":"Factors Affecting Personal Loan Eligibility","answer":"The factors that affect Personal loan eligibility are:\n\n        Monthly Income\n        Age\n        Monthly Expenses\n        Any Other Loan\n        Credit History\n        Job Stability\n        Category of Your Employer"},{"id":"221","question":"factors that affect your personal loan interest rates","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/factors-affecting-personal-loan-interest-rates/https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/factors-affecting-personal-loan-interest-rates/"},{"id":"222","question":"Facts You Need to Know About Credit Card EMIs","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/credit-card/facts-need-know-credit-card-emis/"},{"id":"223","question":"Features & Benefits of Lord Fincap Personal Loan","answer":"        Avail loans from ₹50,000 – 5,00,000\n        Flexible repayment tenure ranging from 12 – 60 months\n        Competitive interest rate\n        No collateral or security required\n        Minimal paperwork and hassle free processing\n        Fast loan approval"},{"id":"224","question":"Features & Benefits of SBM (State Bank of Mysore) Personal Loan","answer":"        Greater Loan Amount\n        Convenient Loan Repayment Options\n        Minimal Documentation\n        Smooth Loan Approvals\n        Low-Interest Rates"},{"id":"225","question":"Features & Benefits of SBP (State Bank of Patiala) Personal Loan","answer":"        Higher Loan Amount\n        Easy Loan Repayment Options\n        Both Residential and Commercial Property Accepted as Collateral\n        Minimal Documentation\n        Faster Loan Approvals\n        Attractive Interest Rates"},{"id":"226","question":"Features & Benefits of SBT (State Bank of Travancore) Personal Loan","answer":"        Higher Loan Amount\n        Convenient Loan Repayment Options\n        Both Residential and Commercial Property accepted as collateral\n        Quick loan approvals\n        Attractive Interest Rates"},{"id":"227","question":"Features & Benefits of State Bank of Bikaner and Jaipur Personal Loan\n","answer":"What makes SBBJ Personal Loan different from others are the following features and benefits:\n\n        Loan Amount ranging from ₹50,000 – 15,00,000\n        Flexible loan repayment options\n        Minimal Documentation\n        Fast Approvals"},{"id":"228","question":"Features & Benefits of Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited Personal Loan ","answer":"        Maximum Loan Amount Availability\n        Convenient Loan Process\n        Easy Repayment Options\n        Minimal Documentation\n        Speedy Approvals\n        Competitive Interest Rates"},{"id":"229","question":"Features & Benefits of Union Bank of India Personal Loan","answer":"                Loan available up to Rs. 10 lakhs\n        Easy repayment options\n        Both Residential and Commercial Property Accepted as Collateral\n        Quick disbursal \n"},{"id":"230","question":"Features and Benefits Vintage Financial Solutions Loan","answer":"        Loan sanctioned for an amount up to ₹15,00,0000\n        Simple procedure\n        minimal documentation and quick approval\n        Loans available for Delhi/ NCR residents only\n        Attractive rate of interest"},{"id":"231","question":"Features of a Home Loan Top-Up","answer":"Read below what are the features of a top-up home loan:\n\n        Available only for an existing home loan borrower.\n        Interest rate starting from 8.70% per annum.\n        Tenure of the loan can go up to the maximum tenure of your home loan (10-20 years)\n        Maximum loan amount depends on the outstanding balance of the existing home loan,\n        The loan amount can be used for different purposes such as buying furniture for your home  or renovation or any other personal need\n        If the money is used for renovation or extension of your home, you can get tax benefit\n        The interest rate on a home loan top-up is low\n        Loan process is smoother for existing borrowers as well as those transferring their home loan\n        There is no mortgage required to submit to the lender for the facility"},{"id":"232","question":"Features of ICICI Bank Student Travel Card","answer":"        Convenient and safe to use\n        Attractive merchant discounts & offers in India and 130 countries and 1,20,000 merchant locations\n        Preferential Forex rates\n        Highly rewarding\n        Alliance offers from ICICI Bank\n        Allows online account management features such as Monthly e-statement\n        Can use this card for withdrawal of cash from more than 1.5 million MasterCard ATMs\n        Membership of International Student Identity Card (ISIC)\n        Destination offers from your membership\n        Easy replacement with Primary Card\n        Comprehensive Travel Insurance"},{"id":"233","question":"Features of SBI Student Plus Advantage Card","answer":"        5% Value Back on Departmental and Grocery spends\n        Accelerated Rewards\n        Ready Cash\n        Worldwide Acceptance\n        Add-on Cards\n        Online Booking of Railway Tickets\n        Utility Bill Payment Facility\n        Balance Transfer on EMI\n        Flexipay\n        Easy Money"},{"id":"234","question":"Financial Reasons Might Prove Hazardous For Your Home Loan Application","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/financial-reasons-might-prove-hazardous-for-your-home-loan-application/https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/financial-reasons-might-prove-hazardous-for-your-home-loan-application/"},{"id":"235","question":"Fixed & Floating Interest Rates of Home Loan Lenders","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/how-to-avoid-home-loan-flat-interest-rate-trap/"},{"id":"236","question":"Fixed Maturity Plans (FMPs)","answer":"Fixed Maturity Plans (FMPs) refer to close-ended debt funds that invest in debt          instruments such as certificates of deposits (Cds), corporate debt and commercial papers (CPs). The low-cost investment vehicle offer features including a pre-specified maturity date, quality debt instrument, lock-in period till the maturity date, risk adjusted returns along with indexation benefits on assets held for a term of 1 year-3 years."},{"id":"237","question":"Flexi payment","answer":"In this mode of payment, you are supposed to make the payment in three phases, first  installment of the money will be deposited at the time of booking, second is required at milestone and third and final payment will be done at the time of possession of the property."},{"id":"238","question":"Formalities Required in Personal Loan Balance Transfer","answer":"The balance transfer is executed by completing the necessary formalities.\n\n        Request the existing lender to issue you a No-objection Certificate (NOC) with respect to the loan transfer to the new lender\n        Also ask the existing lender to present you with a statement showing the loan paid so far, the outstanding loan balance, the rate of interest charged, the remaining tenure left, etc.\n        Present these documents to the new lender to process your balance transfer application\n        The new lender would go through the repayment track before approving this loan arrangement"},{"id":"239","question":"Fulfillment of Financial Goals","answer":"A mutual fund is an appropriate investment vehicle to achieve your financial goals like the purchase of a home, emergency corpus, vacation funds, education & marriage of your kids, and even the income generation needs."},{"id":"240","question":"Fund of Funds","answer":"A Fund of Funds (FOF) also known as a Multi-Manager Investment, is a type of investment strategy in which a fund is invested in other types of funds. The portfolio of this investment contains different underlying assets instead allowing you to invest directly in stocks, bonds and other types of securities.\n\n        Here the funds are invested in mutual funds directly, instead of assets.\n        Your investment is diversified in the mutual funds instead of market instruments.\n        The returns will be an average of all the funds."},{"id":"241","question":"Get an insight of debt fund SIPs","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/get-insight-debt-fund-sips/"},{"id":"242","question":"Gilt Funds","answer":"These are the funds which invest only in government securities and are preferred by conservative investors. Since these funds invest in secure government bonds, hence investors are protected from credit risk.\n\n        Investment is completely in government securities\n        The value of gilt funds units is dictated by the market volatility."},{"id":"243","question":"gilt funds","answer":"It is always nice to invest in mutual funds as the money gets diversified across different securities to reduce the risk element. Fund managers undertake the task of constantly moving your investments from stocks to bonds to money market instruments and thus ensure reduction of investment risk. Broadly, mutual funds are classified into equity and debt funds. Equity funds mainly invest in stocks and equity related products, while debt funds pool the money mainly in government & corporate bonds, as well as other debt securities.\n\nGilt funds are the part of debt mutual funds that primarily invest in government securities. The funds also invest in state government securities and treasury bills. However, the operational methodology of gilt funds is entirely different from traditional debt funds. Where normal debt funds invest across all the debt instruments, gilt funds make investment specifically in government securities. Acting as a sovereign paper, they mitigate the credit risk of investors. Gilt funds provide retail investors an easy way and cheaper way to invest in government securities, which are purchased mostly by the institutional investors. As an investor, you can choose between short-term and long-term gilt funds based on the investment horizon you have."},{"id":"244","question":"Give me Loan.","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"245","question":"Global Funds","answer":"It is a type of closed-end fund or you can say exchange traded fund, which invests in companies located anywhere in the world. These funds offer more global opportunities for the diversification and act as a hedge against currency risks and inflation.\n\n        In global funds, the funds are invested in the assets outside of India.\n        It adds an additional layer in the domestic diversification.\n        It is for those investors, who know the international market as well as the risks involved."},{"id":"246","question":"Gold ETFs\n","answer":"These ETFs aim to track the domestic physical gold price, trades like a common stock on a stock exchange. Gold ETFs(units) experience price changes throughout the day as they are bought and sold."},{"id":"247","question":"Gold ETFs\n","answer":"Gold ETFs refer to a mechanism by which you can get involved in the gold bullion market. The investment in Gold ETFs gets converted into papers without any physical delivery of the yellow metal. Like shares, you can buy or sell Gold ETFs on the stock exchanges. The price per unit of the Gold ETF is equivalent to 1 or sometimes even half a gram of the yellow metal on the day of allotment. Gold GTF value depends on the prices of the yellow metal. As gold prices surge, the ETF value will rise and vice-e-versa."},{"id":"248","question":"Goldman Sachs Mutual Fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/goldman-sachs-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"249","question":"Guide to reduce risks in mutual fund investments","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/guide-reduce-risks-mutual-fund-investments/"},{"id":"250","question":"HDFC ForexPlus Card","answer":"        HDFC ForexPlus Card is tailor made for any student who studies abroad and needs finance in different currencies. This card works just like a credit card, the transaction amount will be debited from the HDFC ForexPlus Card balance directly.\n        The card is available in ten currencies which are accepted all over the world and thus you can change them into the currency of the nation you are currently in. It has acceptability in all merchant outlets which are affiliated to Visa or MasterCard.  When you carry out any transaction in the card currency you won’t suffer due to the swinging market rates.\n        In case you’re not a HDFC bank customer you need not worry. You still can avail this card, all you need to do is visit your nearest HDFC branch with the required documents."},{"id":"251","question":"HDFC Moneyback Card","answer":"Get cashbacks on everyday spends with HDFC Moneyback Card\n\nAnnual Fee: ₹500\n\nPrivileges & Perks\n\n        Get 2x reward points on online spends\n        Spend ₹50,000 in a quarter and get ₹500 e-voucher\n        Redeem rewards as cashbacks\n        2 reward points on ₹150 spend\n        Enjoy a Fuel Surcharge Waiver of up to 1% on all fuel transactions above ₹ 400\n        Enjoy 50 days long interest-free period from the date of purchase"},{"id":"252","question":"HDFC MoneyBack Credit Card","answer":"The reward points can even be redeemed for exciting gifts, air miles and attractive offers from HDFC’s gift catalogue. 100% more reward points are there on online spends. You can even enjoy a fuel surcharge waiver on transactions worth more than ₹400.\n\nAnnual Fee – As Applicable by the bank\nWhat’s Special About the Card?\n\nReward points and the scope to redeem them for cashback, gifts, air miles and several other attractive offers make many choose this card."},{"id":"253","question":"HDFC Multicurrency Platinum ForexPlus Chip Card","answer":"This card is simply perfect for students who have multi- destination traveling needs and want to carry 23 currencies on one single card. Yes, you heard it right. You can keep 23 foreign currencies in your HDFC Multicurrency Platinum ForexPlus Chip Card, thereby saving your money and time. This provides you complete protection against any kind of foreign exchange rate fluctuation in the near future. You also receive an insurance cover of Rs. 5 Lakh for any kind of misuse of card, accident or fraud."},{"id":"254","question":"History of SIP (Systematic Investment Plan) in India","answer":"The history of SIP in India is two-decade old when Franklin Templeton India Asset Management (India) Ltd launched the same along with Templeton India Growth Fund in 1996. The SIP allowed investors to make a fixed sum of investment each month. Soon, other fund houses began to offer SIPs in their equity funds. At the start, investors were made to make payment via post-dated cheques. Subsequent to the arrival to electronic clearing system (ECS) facility, AMCs began to take bank mandates from investors. Currently, most AMCs do not entertain post-dated cheques and insist on ECS, a facility by which money is automatically debited from the account as per the standing instructions."},{"id":"255","question":"Home Loan Tax Benefit Calculator","answer":"Tax benefits work on a dual basis when it comes to a home loan. Means, the benefits are applicable to both principal and interest repayments under different sections of the Income Tax Act. While tax deductions on principal repayments are allowed as per Section 80C of the IT Act, Section 24 comes into the picture by offering tax exemption on interest repayments. As the ramifications of taxation with respect to home loan is slightly intricate in nature, we will slowly but gradually disseminating the information to let you understand the concept clearly. So, without wasting any time, let’s start evaluating the tax benefits as per both the sections."},{"id":"256","question":"Home Loan: Pick the Right Bank to Live Tension Free","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/home-loan-pick-the-right-bank-to-live-tension-free/"},{"id":"257","question":"how  is your day?","answer":"Well, It was hectic till now as i am helping others."},{"id":"258","question":"how are you?\n","answer":"I am doing  nice work, tell me about you."},{"id":"259","question":"How can you apply for home loan top-up?","answer":"The process to apply for a home loan top-up is very simple. You can simply request your lender to provide you a certain amount over and above your existing home loan amount. If you have maintained a good repayment track record, you will get the approval for this facility and the disbursalreally soon."},{"id":"260","question":"How can you reduce capital gain tax with indexation?","answer":"As we now get to know that the indexed cost of acquisition or the inflation adjusted price is dependent upon the ratio of the cost of inflation index at the time of booking profit to its value. So, higher the number it will be, lower will be the tax you pay. Inflation also adds up over a period of time so it can result in massive reduction in the taxable amount. Inflation can eat up small gains over a long period of time. In that case, you may not have to pay any tax."},{"id":"261","question":"How do gold ETFs work?","answer":"Based on the cost of gold per gram during the allotment, the amount of money you would like to invest in Gold ETFs will determine the quantity of units that will be allocated to you. For instance-your overall investment fund amount is Rs 30,000 and on a certain date, the per gram price of gold is Rs 950, then the number of units that will be allocated to you is 31 (approx)."},{"id":"262","question":"how do you Classifty loan provided by wishfin.","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"263","question":"how do you Classify Loan?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"264","question":"how do you do","answer":""},{"id":"265","question":"How Does the Floating Interest Rate Work on a Home Loan?","answer":"The floating interest rate implies that the rate of interest would change based on the prevailing market conditions. Usually, when the RBI changes the repo rate, the rate at which the central bank lends to commercial banks, you can see lenders revising the interest rates. The floating rates are also impacted based on the internal cost of banks. When the repo rate and internal cost decrease, the lending rates fall and increase the other way round. The interest rate changes would mean the changes in principal and interest portions of the Equated Monthly Installment (EMI). As the rate comes down, the interest portion of the EMI would come down. When the rate goes up, the interest portion will be deducted more, yet keeping the installment amount same in both the situations."},{"id":"266","question":"How is capital gain ascertained?","answer":"The government has constructed an index known as the cost of inflation index (CII). The base year of the index is 1981-82 and the value for the year is 100. The value of index gets declared each financial year. The ratio of inflation index at the time of sale of the investment to the value at the time of purchase is taken into consideration while calculating long-term capital gain. The value so obtained is multiplied by the cost of the acquisition of the investment. Thus, you get the indexed cost of acquisition or say inflation adjusted purchase price, which then subtracted from the sale consideration to obtain capital gain/loss.\n\nFormula for inflation adjusted price=Purchase Price × CII of the year sold/CII of the year purchased\n\nCapital Gain/Loss=Sale Consideration -Inflation Adjusted Price\n\nFor example– If you had purchased a debt mutual fund scheme at Rs 50,000 on 20th April 2013 and its maturity was on April 2014, then the capital gain thus ascertained would have been in accordance with the ratio of 1024 and 939, the cost of inflation index for FY 2014-15 and FY 2013-14, respectively. The ratio was (1024/939)=1.09. Inflation adjusted price would have been be Rs 20,000×1.09=Rs 21,800. If the investment offered a return of 10% per annum, then sale consideration would have been Rs 22,000. Capital gain would have been Rs 22,000-Rs 21,800=Rs 200"},{"id":"267","question":"How is CIBIL Report Generated?","answer":"Credit Information Bureau of India Limited (CIBIL), India’s first Credit Information Company collects and maintains the records of individual’s and non-individual’s (commercial entities) credit related transactions such as loans and credit cards. These records are provided by banks and other lenders on a monthly basis to the Credit Bureau. Using this information a Credit Information Report (CIR) and Credit Score is developed. This enables the lenders to evaluate and approve loan applications based on the past record."},{"id":"268","question":"How is credit score calculated?","answer":"The member banks and financial institutions monthly report the details related to credit activity of the customers to the bureaus. This includes data of each loan or credit card repayment made by the customer during the period and even the late or skipped payments. The report comprises of new loan applications, interest rate, credit limit on card, the status of all loan accounts including those ‘written-off’ or ‘settled’ or ‘closed’. After the complex statistical analysis of the provided information credit score is calculated. If credit payment is done on time then the score is good. The candidates with high credit score have the better chances of getting a loan or credit card."},{"id":"269","question":"how many categories of loan can i get?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"270","question":"how many categories of loan do wishfin provide?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"271","question":"how many categoris of loan can i get from wishfin ?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"272","question":"how many types of load can i get from wishfin ?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"273","question":"how many types of loan can i get?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"274","question":"how many types of loan do wishfin provide?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"275","question":"How much loan can i get ?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"276","question":"How much loan can i get from wishfin ?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"277","question":"How much loan can Wishfin provide me ?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"278","question":"How much loan can you provide me ?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"279","question":"How SIPs Have Performed in Election Years","answer":"If we consider the tenure of UPA government in 2009-2014, there was a 67% Sensex return over 5 years. Investing during this tenure led to 30% annual return returns for mutual funds’ owners. For instance, if you would have invested INR 10,000 during that tenure (Before 2009 election), you may have received approximately INR 35,000 in return."},{"id":"280","question":"How to Avail a Personal Loan for Salary Less than fifteen thousand","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/how-to-avail-personal-loan-with-less-salary/"},{"id":"281","question":"How to Avoid Fixed Rate?","answer":"If you are yet to take a home loan, then you should ask the bank to disburse the same on a floating rate. If you are into the fixed rate regime, you can ask the bank to get it converted into a floating rate. You need to pay a conversion fee at around 2% of the outstanding balance. So, on an assumed outstanding loan balance of ₹20 lakhs, the fee would be ₹40,000. Pay the fee and start servicing the loan on a floating basis."},{"id":"282","question":"How to Avoid Home Loan Flat Interest Rate Trap?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/how-to-avoid-home-loan-flat-interest-rate-trap/"},{"id":"283","question":"How to Avoid Personal Loan Traps","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/how-to-avoid-personal-loan-traps/"},{"id":"284","question":"How To Buy Home In Other City? Simple Tips","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/how-to-buy-home-in-other-city-simple-tips-for-hassle-free-journey/"},{"id":"285","question":"How to Check CIBIL score by PAN Card?","answer":"You can check your CIBIL by Permanent Account Number (PAN) and some basic details. The score can be checked within 2 minutes by following the simple steps mentioned below.\n\n        Go to CIBIL score page at wishfin.com\n        Enter your Name as per PAN Card\n        Mention correct Date of Birth\n        Select Gender\n        Provide PAN Card number\n        Enter contact details such as email address, residence address and mobile number\n        Agree to the terms and condition\n        Click on submit button"},{"id":"286","question":"How to Check CIBIL Score on WhatsApp","answer":"Step 1: Give a Missed Call on 8287 151 151\nStep 2: Your number will be added on WhatsApp Chat\nStep 3: Start the process by entering your NAME, Date of Birth & Gender\nStep 4: Type Your PAN Number (don’t worry your details will remain safe and secure)\nStep 5: Type Your Residential Address (similar to your banking details)\nStep 6: Provide Your City of Residence, followed by State and Pincode\nStep 7: And, lastly your Email ID\nStep 8: You can see your latest CIBIL Score right in your WhatsApp chat box"},{"id":"287","question":"How to Check Free CIBIL Score Online?","answer":"To get free CIBIL score online the customer can login on the official website of the credit agency and request for the report. Also, to get the report the customer has to furnish the required documents. It is only after the verification of documents that the customer will receive the CIR through email. The report will be sent within a day.\n\nHowever, there is an easy and quick alternate where you can check CIBIL score by PAN Card only and no other documentation is required. Moreover, you don’t have to pay any fees and get free credit health check. It is not necessary that only the Bank or financial institution can check the CIBIL score. An individual too can check CIBIL score and get the CIBIL/Credit report online at Wishfin. Just follow the simple steps mentioned below:"},{"id":"288","question":"How to earn through Mutual Fund SIP?","answer":"If you start investing 20-30% of your salary, it is expected that you can make your first million even before you get married that is in general before you turn 30. To reach that level, start investing in mutual fund SIP with ₹5,000 if your monthly salary is ₹25,000. Here is the plan that you can follow to make ₹10 lakhs with the minimum investment of ₹5,000 per month.\n\n        Invest ₹5,000 in a good short-term debt fund (Debt funds has no TDS)\n        Increase the amount by 10% annually for two years\n        Now invest in equity funds and don’t forget to increase the amount by 10% annually\n        Follow this pattern and you will make ₹10 lakhs in just 8 years!"},{"id":"289","question":"How to Get a Home Loan with a Bad Credit?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/how-to-get-a-home-loan-with-a-bad-credit/"},{"id":"290","question":"How to get double indexation benefit?","answer":"Suppose you made an investment of Rs 40,000 in FMP in March 2014 of FY 2013-14 and redeemed the same in April 2015 of FY 2015-16. If the rate of return on the investment was 10%, the redemption value of the fund must have been Rs 43,200. The index cost of acquisition will take into the consideration the inflation index for FY 2013-14 and FY 2015-16. The CII for FY 2013-14 and FY 2015-16 are 939 and 1081, respectively. Indexed cost of acquisition thus would have been Rs 40,000×1081/939=Rs 46,049. The long-term capital gain would have been Rs 46,049-Rs 43,200=-Rs 2,849. Here, you would have faced a capital loss of Rs 2,849. There would not have been any tax liability on the same. But since it is a loss, you have the provision of carrying forward this for 8 years or offset with long-term capital gains."},{"id":"291","question":"How to get Personal Loan with Bad /Low Credit Score","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/how-to-get-a-personal-loan-with-bad-credit/"},{"id":"292","question":"How to Improve CIBIL Score?","answer":"In order to get best deals on credit cards and loans, it is important that your credit score is good. In India, lenders such as banks and NBFCs would consider your application suitable for the credit facility only if you have a good credit score. It is also true that most of the people do not have a credit history and still avail the service but the fact is that they are not eligible for the best deals. Thus, maintaining a good credit score becomes important. There are different measures to improve your CIBIL score some of which are mentioned below:\n\n        Pay credit card bills on time\n        Make sure EMI deductions (if any) are successful\n        Avoid unnecessary expenditure\n        Apply for a loan or credit card"},{"id":"293","question":"How to manage risks?","answer":"        Choose a bond fund that does not change frequently with its duration\n        Select a bond fund that has duration closer to your investment horizon\n        Choose bond funds that may have invested in corporate bonds, which would have less exposure to credit risks.\n        Find the bonds that would have performed well during the downturn of the economy"},{"id":"294","question":"How to Reduce Your Personal Loan Burden Without Affecting Your Wallet?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/tips-to-reduce-personal-loan-burden/"},{"id":"295","question":"How to save more money each month?","answer":"Here are the habits to adapt to save on a monthly basis:\n\n        Follow a strict monthly budget plan\n        Buy insurance for your family as well for yourselves\n        Use credit cards (if any) in the case of unavoidable cases only\n        Make investments"},{"id":"296","question":"How to save more money on a tight budget?","answer":"If you are on a tight budget but want to save, do not think that you are out of options. You can invest even a small amount and get good returns if you can manage it in a disciplined. If you can save even as low as ₹1000 on a monthly basis, you can invest in mutual fund SIP. Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) is a platform that encourages you to save a part of your income regularly without pressurizing yourself and affecting your other financial liabilities. If you continue to follow the routine, you could end up saving a lump sum amount that can help you attain your financial objectives."},{"id":"297","question":"How to Select a Mutual Fund?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/select-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"298","question":"i do not  want to talk to you","answer":"I will try to  better assist you next time."},{"id":"299","question":"I want a Loan from Wishfin.","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"300","question":"I want a Loan from you.","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"301","question":"I want a Loan.","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"302","question":"ICICI Bank Coral Credit Card","answer":"Every anniversary year will accumulate 10,000 PAYBACK points for you. And if you are a movie buff, you will like this card even more. It’s because you can get 2 complimentary movie tickets every month under the Buy One Get One Offer at BookMyShow. It also provides one complimentary domestic railway and airport lounge visit in a quarter.\n\nAnnual Fee – ₹500 +18% GST\nWhat’s Special About the Card?\n\nThe PAYBACK points on spends at groceries, dining, supermarkets, and even on the anniversary year give the card its share of brownie points. With the addition of movie tickets and lounge access to the list of offers, the card makes it too tempting for the shoppers to resist.\n"},{"id":"303","question":"ICICI Bank Student Travel Card","answer":"        ICICI Bank Student Travel Card is a blessing in disguise for you if you wish to study in abroad. You can use this credit card to pay your application and university fees either online or through a physical swipe.  The card is very convenient to use since it allows you to manage your living expenses and is accepted at all outlets that take a MasterCard. You can withdraw cash from over 1.5 million MasterCard ATMs through this card.\n        You are entitled to an International Student Identity Card free membership which will give you access to different discount benefits along with exciting destination offers. The tempting merchant offers and discounts will be available in 131 countries including India.You are also bound to get benefits from a travel insurance, advantageous forex rates, and other alliance offers from the bank."},{"id":"304","question":"ICICI HPCL Coral Credit Card","answer":"Reduce your fuel bills by earning maximum rewards\n\nAnnual Fee: ₹199\n\nPrivileges & Perks\n\n        Earn 2 PAYBACK points on every purchase worth ₹100 (except fuel)\n        You can redeem 2000 PAYBACK points in a go which would be worth ₹500\n        With every fuel purchase at HPCL, you can earn 2.5% cashback and 1% surcharge waiver\n        A minimum 15% savings on dining at more than 800 restaurants across India, courtesy Culinary Treats Program\n        A cashback of 2.5% on fuel refill at HPCL stations on a minimum transaction of ₹500"},{"id":"305","question":"Importance of good CIBIL score","answer":"A good credit score makes a person eligible for better deals on loans and credit cards. Having a good CIBIL score not only gives access to more options, it is also an important factor in deciding payment habits of individuals. Credit facilities such as a credit card or loan are provided based on the present employment status of the customer also on their CIBIL score."},{"id":"306","question":"Important things to consider before transferring home loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/important-things-consider-transferring-home-loan/"},{"id":"307","question":"Improve Your Chances of Getting Mortgage with 6 Simple Ways","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/improve-your-chances-of-getting-mortgage-with-6-simple-ways/"},{"id":"308","question":"In mutual funds, you can make money in three ways.","answer":"Dividend payment :\nCorporation earns profit and reinvest the same in business and share a fraction of profit with share holders in the form of a dividend.\n\n• Capital gains distribution :\nThere are two types of capital gains, short term and long term capital gains. These gains are distributed to the shareholders and the distribution is declared at the end of the year.\n\n• NAV :\nNAV stands for Net Asset Value, which results from the difference between the assets and liabilities of the fund. Mutual fund’s selling and buying process is based on NAV of the trade date. It is calculated by dividing the current market value of the fund with the number of outstanding units."},{"id":"309","question":"Income Funds","answer":"Income funds are long-term debt schemes that mainly invest in government bonds, corporate bonds and money market instruments. These funds are highly vulnerable to interest rate changes and are apt for those having long-term investment horizon and higher-risk appetite.\n\n        If you fall under 10% or 20%tax slab, try to invest in these funds.\n        The long-term capital gains on investments held over 3 years are taxed at 20% with indexation benefit.\n        In case you fall under 30% tax slab, these funds can offer better post- tax returns.\n"},{"id":"310","question":"Index Funds","answer":"Also known as index tracker, these funds have the portfolio constructed to match or track the components of a market index. These types of funds provide broader market exposure and low operating expenses.\n\n        Index funds are designed to replicate the portfolio of the market index such as BSE SENSEX, NSE Nifty.\n        The risk involved is proportionate to the index fluctuations.\n        No fund manager is there for help and support."},{"id":"311","question":"Insta Loan","answer":"In a world where nothing is certain, financial emergencies can creep anytime to haunt you. At that moment, even your dear ones who used to care for you before can sway away from providing any help, leaving you in utter despair. But not the banks that have Insta Loan ready for you to grab and resolve the financial emergency you can get stuck with. By the term, it clearly means the loan would get credited to the account instantly, much unlike the regular loans that take around 3-4 days to get disbursed. Actually, it’s a pre-approved loan amount based on your relationship with a particular lender. There are several banks that offer this facility."},{"id":"312","question":"Insta Loan Available/ Provided at These Lenders/ Banks","answer":"You can get an instant loan at the following banks\n\n        HDFC Bank\n        ICICI Bank\n        Bajaj FInserv"},{"id":"313","question":"Insta Loan Ready to Resolve All Your Fast Cash Emergencies","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/insta-loan-for-fast-cash-emergencies/"},{"id":"314","question":"Interest rates on Loan Against Property","answer":"The interest rates applicable on loan against property are fixed as well floating. Just like a housing loan, a borrower can choose which rate system is convenient for them. The rates are, however, quite high as compared to home loans."},{"id":"315","question":"Inverse relationship between interest rate and bond prices","answer":""},{"id":"316","question":"Investing for a Longer Term","answer":"The money invested in equity mutual funds is put into the high return proposition of equities. To achieve the investment fruition you need to stay invested for a long period, preferably for more than 3 years."},{"id":"317","question":"Investment Mantra for youngsters","answer":"Youngsters have the opportunity to invest more as they have no major financial responsibilities. But, they still have to take care of their own expenses. So, if you want to really succeed in life is to follow the below mantra:\n\nIncome – Savings = Expenses\n\nThe above equation has brought the difference between a successful person and an ordinary one. So, the first thing you should do after you get your salary is the investment, and then use the remaining for your expenditure."},{"id":"318","question":"Investors of these Top-performing Schemes Enjoyed a Return of 6%-10% in the Last Week","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/investors-top-performing-schemes-enjoyed-return-6-10-last-week/"},{"id":"319","question":"Is Balance Transfer of a Personal Loan Beneficial for Me?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/is-balance-transfer-of-personal-loan-beneficial/"},{"id":"320","question":"Is home loan overdraft facility a good option?","answer":"Home loan overdraft facility is good option, if you are very much sure that you will be able to save some extra money every month after paying the regular EMI. It will help in reducing the loan amount along with tenure. Under this facility, you can deposit any surplus money that you have into the home loan account, though you have the option to withdraw the money if required,is the biggest advantage. By depositing the money higher than the EMI will help in saving on total interest outgo in long run.\n\nPoints to consider:\n\n        Works as current account with overdraft limit\n        Offer higher liquidity on the deposited amount\n        Upto 25 basis points higher rate of interest\n        Regular transactions are necessary for higher benefits\n        Good option for double income families\n        Reduced interest liability without losing tax benefits\n        Facility to withdraw the surplus money any time"},{"id":"321","question":"Is Home Loan Tax Deductible?\n","answer":"To their delight, let me inform that tax deductions are allowed on a home loan. But how does tax benefits pan out in your home loan journey, is something you need to understand for a pleasant stay at your searched house."},{"id":"322","question":"Is SIP (Systematic Investment Plan) a Better Investment Option than One -Time Investment?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/is-sip-better-than-one-time-investment/"},{"id":"323","question":"Is Wishfin an Authentic Partner of CIBIL?","answer":"Wishfin is first official fintech partner of TransUnion CIBIL – the company that provides you your official CIBIL score. We are sharing below the screenshot of the authentic partnership by CIBIL. You can also check it on the CIBIL website through this url below.\nhttps://www.cibil.com/official-partners"},{"id":"324","question":"jai shree ram","answer":"jai shree ram"},{"id":"325","question":"JM Financial Mutual Fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/jm-financial-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"326","question":"JM Financial Mutual Fund Customer Care Number","answer":"Feel free to contact the help desk of JM Financial Mutual Fund. Don't let your queries, doubts & confusion to remain unresolved? Call 1800-1038-345 or drop in your email on the ID as shown on the website of JM Financial Mutual Fund. The charges for using a toll free number is incurred by JM Financial Mutual Fund irrespective of the call duration."},{"id":"327","question":"JM Financial Mutual Fund Customer Login","answer":"Are you gaining sufficient returns or losing your possible returns in bullish market? You need to check out your investments before it gets too late. Get your email ID registered on the portal of JM Financial Mutual Fund and check where your stocks and funds are heading to? The snapshot of all your investments give you a clear picture for deciding whether to invest or not in particular funds or you need to switch to other funds or to redeem. It becomes easier for you, not to lose track of stock market fundamentals but to bet for the right opportunities within time. JM Financial Mutual fund Customer login makes it possible for you by giving you safe, simple, user-friendly, secure and efficient platform which gives an investor a pleasant experience, also at the same time reducing the paper work load. You need to get registered with your PAN number in mutual fund folio for getting access to transactions."},{"id":"328","question":"JP Morgan Mutual Fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/jp-morgan-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"329","question":"just get lost","answer":"what i did"},{"id":"330","question":"Know how mutual fund investment can bolster your financial portfolio","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/know-mutual-fund-investment-can-bolster-financial-portfolio/"},{"id":"331","question":"Kotak Mutual Fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/kotak-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"332","question":"Large Cap Funds","answer":"These types of equity funds invest a larger proportion of their corpus in companies having large market capitalization. Though the criteria for large cap companies may vary as per their assets. These funds are best known to offer stable and sustainable returns to the investors over a period of time."},{"id":"333","question":"Liquid Funds","answer":"These are the types of debt funds that invest in securities with a residual maturity of upto 91 days. The assets invested in these funds are not tied-up for a long time, thus it further helps the fund manager in meeting the redemption demands of investors.\n\n        Want to invest in a fund offering high liquidity? If yes, look no further than investing in liquid funds.\n        These funds offer liquidity to the investor/s by investing in liquid instruments such as treasury bills, certificates of deposits, commercial papers, etc.\n        Liquid funds invest in securities having a residual maturity of upto 91 days."},{"id":"334","question":"Liquidity","answer":"Mutual funds offer a high degree of liquidity by allowing investors to redeem as and when they deem fit to do so. Of the mutual funds, liquid funds top the chart in terms of liquidity by allowing instant redemption wherein the money comes to the bank accounts instantly."},{"id":"335","question":"list of charges that ULIP investment has:","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/know-ulip-charges/"},{"id":"336","question":"list of credit cards for which you can apply on WhatsApp.","answer":"Here’s a list of credit cards for which you can apply on WhatsApp.\n\n        SBI Credit Card\n        HDFC Credit Card\n        Standard Chartered Credit Card\n        American Express Credit Card\n        ICICI Credit Card\n        RBL Bank Credit Card"},{"id":"337","question":"Loan Against Property Definition","answer":"As the name suggests, a loan taken against a property or mortgage is defined as a loan against property. The main difference between a home loan and loan against property is that a home loan is taken for the property and mortgage loan is taken against the property. The loan is given on the basis of the property value as per the market. You can use the fund for any legitimate purposes be it an emergency or a planned expenditure such as business expansion, marriage, travel or medical purposes.\n"},{"id":"338","question":"Loan in One Day is Possible at These Banks","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/loan-in-1-day-available-at-these-lenders/"},{"id":"339","question":"Loan Scheme for Housewife","answer":"Are you a housewife who is looking for a loan but don’t know which schemes are there for you? If that is the case, all you need to do is just go through the points below:\n\nStar Mahila Gold Loan Scheme\n\nThis scheme is provided by the Bank of India that helps non-working women or housewives to purchase gold ornaments.\n\nPradhan Mantri Mudra Yojana for Women\n\nThis scheme is launched by the Government of India, whose main endeavor is to improve the status of the women by providing them loans and encouraging them to start new ventures. There are many lending financial bodies and banks that offer mudra loans to the eligible applicants.\n\nGold Loan\n\nBeing a homemaker or housewife if you have some gold jewellery, you can use this asset in order to take a loan against the same. There are many lenders out there that offer you this facility at an attractive interest rate so that your needs can be fulfilled."},{"id":"340","question":"Loan Subsidy Scheme","answer":"Under this scheme, 25% of the loan amount will be subsidized by the State Government. Well, this scheme is not available across all States."},{"id":"341","question":"Loan?","answer":"Loan is a thing that is borrowed, especially a sum of money that is expected to be paid back with interest. Do you want some? [yes,No]"},{"id":"342","question":"Lord Fincap Personal Loan","answer":"Require the funds to fulfil your dreams of purchasing a car, own a house or to go on a vacation. Apply for a personal loan at the Lord Fincap and turn your dreams into reality. The company provides collateral-free loans to fulfill the urgent financial needs of the people by extending the funds up to ₹5 lacs at the reasonable rate of interest."},{"id":"343","question":"Lord Fincap Personal Loan Details","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/lord-fincap-personal-loan/"},{"id":"344","question":"Lord Fincap Personal Loan EMI Calculator","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/lord-fincap-personal-loan/"},{"id":"345","question":"Lump Sum Amount Investment in Mutual Fund","answer":"The investor can invest money in a mutual fund through a single transaction if they have a large corpus to invest. The features of one-time investment are:\n\n        It is rewarding in the long term therefore, the investment horizon should be kept long\n        It is an ideal option for people who can take risk in anticipation of high returns\n        It helps in meeting financial goals\n        The investment is made by issuing a single cheque of the lump sum investment amount"},{"id":"346","question":"Massive Capital Growth Prospects, Tax Benefits","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/elss-perfect-investment-for-future/"},{"id":"347","question":"Maximum Advantages with Budget Investment","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/ready-move-property-maximum-advantages-budget-investment/"},{"id":"348","question":"Maximum Loan amount you can get on a mortgage loan","answer":"Unlike a home loan where you can get a maximum of 90% loan amount, the maximum limit for a loan taken against property is 60% of the property value. The amount may vary depending on the property location and income of the borrower."},{"id":"349","question":"Meaning of Loan?","answer":"Loan is a thing that is borrowed, especially a sum of money that is expected to be paid back with interest. Do you want some? [yes,No]"},{"id":"350","question":"Mid Cap Funds","answer":"The mid cap funds are a type of stock funds that invest in mid-sized companies. Talking about a company’s size, it is determined by its market capitalization. Recommended for those who are willing to take the risk."},{"id":"351","question":"Mint 50 Best Funds – Mutual Fund Schemes To Invest In","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/mint-50-best-funds-schemes-to-invest-in/"},{"id":"352","question":"Mortage Loan Processing Time and Fees","answer":"Since the loan is sanctioned by keeping the property as a collateral, the processing is smoother. However, there is a loan processing fee which in general is maximum up to 1% of the loan amount + GST (18% of the processing fee)."},{"id":"353","question":"Multi-Cap Funds","answer":"These funds invest in companies across the market capitalization. The scope for diversification here is massive as money is invested across stocks of different capitalization. These funds are less risky due to the diversification of money."},{"id":"354","question":"Mutual Fund SIP is a Great Way to Introduce Savings Into Your Routine","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/mutual-fund-sip-investment-savings-routine/"},{"id":"355","question":"my name is _______","answer":"hello ____"},{"id":"356","question":"namaste","answer":"that means Hello in hindi"},{"id":"357","question":"National Savings Certificate (NSC)","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/compare-elss-and-other-tax-saving-schemes/"},{"id":"358","question":"NAV (Net Asset Value) Calculation","answer":"The assets are generally divided into two categories-securities & cash. The securities include both stocks and bonds. Thus, the total asset value of the fund will consist of stocks, bonds and cash at market value. Total assets will be the sum of dividends and interest accrued as well as the liquid assets. The assets also include the liabilities such as money due to creditors as well as other outstanding expenses. Check below the formula of NAV.\n\nNAV=Assets-Debts/Number of outstanding units\n\nAssets=Market value of mutual fund investments+receivables+accrued income\n\nDebts=Liabilities+Outstanding expenses\n\nThe market value of stocks and debentures is generally the closing price of the units on the stock exchange."},{"id":"359","question":"Parag Parikh Long Term Value Fund","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/ppfas-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"360","question":"Pay credit card debt via personal loan to save more on interest","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/pay-credit-card-debt-via-personal-loan-save-interest/"},{"id":"361","question":"Perfect time to take SIP (Systematic Investment Plan)","answer":"SIP mutual fund will benefit you as long as markets remain volatile or exhibiting the downward trend. Moment, the market sets into a bull run and starts rising, SIP won't be of much avail and may offer you less returns compared to the lump sum investments."},{"id":"362","question":"Personal Loan for CIBIL Defaulters","answer":"If we talk about personal loan for CIBIL defaulter, yes it is true that many reputed banks and financial institutions offer credit to such applicants by taking into consideration many factors. Individuals working in a reputed company and getting a handsome monthly income can grab the personal loan deal even though he/she is a defaulter. Well, you will be surprised to know that there are those lenders available in the market that offer personal loan for low CIBIL score. But here is a catch! These types of lenders offer the credit at higher interest rates. Yes, that’s right! The borrower have to avail the loan at higher rates and similarly have to pay the higher EMIs and interest as well."},{"id":"363","question":"Personal Loan for Unemployed","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/personal-loan-for-unemployed/"},{"id":"364","question":"Personal Loan without CIBIL Verification Check","answer":"Getting a personal loan without CIBIL check might be possible if the income of an applicant is good, he/she works in a prestigious Fortune 500 company or applicant’s spouse credit score is high. Not only this, if you are a credit card user and you know how to use your card smartly by paying your dues timely without any default, it could also be a reason why lenders don’t go for CIBIL check even though you don’t have a loan history. The practice of paying the credit card bills timely ultimately helps in boosting your CIBIL, hence enhance your profile in the eyes of lenders.\n\nIf that is the case with you, wait for the good news to come as in that case some lenders might not check the CIBIL. However, usually in most of the cases, lenders do check the credit score of an applicant before availing the loan.\n"},{"id":"365","question":"Personal Loan without CIBIL Verification Score","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/personal-loan-without-cibil-score-verification/"},{"id":"366","question":"Portfolio Diversification","answer":"One of the factors that let a mutual fund stands out from the clutter is its ability to diversify the investments across a wide range of equity and debt instruments. While the equity instruments appreciate the growth of the money, the debt counterparts ensure regular income for the investors.\n\nA fund manager checks the track record of the securities and chooses those that have performed excellently in both good and bad situations. The greater diversification heightens the scope for massive returns on the invested capital."},{"id":"367","question":"PPFAS Mutual Fund Online Login\n","answer":"Simply fill up your details online and obtain your User ID and password, to get started experiencing seamless investing in PPFAS Asset Mutual Fund Schemes."},{"id":"368","question":"Pre-approved home loan","answer":"When you think that it is not affordable to buy a home because of the shooting price of the property and higher rate of interest. The different mode of payment as down payment plan, construction-linked plan, flexi payment plan and time linked payment plan and construction linked payment plan come as a relief for future buyers. Under these options you can book your dream property. It is a win-win situation for both the builders and customers who actually buy it."},{"id":"369","question":"Prepayment Charges for mortgage loan","answer":"Lenders can not charge any prepayment fee for any loan linked to floating rate of interest. But, there is a fee for loans linked to fixed rate. Any individual borrower or co-borrower can prepay his/her loan against property without paying any fee."},{"id":"370","question":"Prime Minister Rozgar Yojana","answer":"Under this scheme, the Government of India offers loans to unemployed so that they can kick-start their own venture. Anyone who is educated till 8th standard is eligible to apply for a loan under this scheme. Individuals aged between 18-35, who are unemployed can avail a loan of up to Rs.5 Lakh. However, in such a case, the income of the beneficiary along with the income of his/her parents should not exceed Rs.1 Lakh per annum."},{"id":"371","question":"Private or PSU Banks","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/home-loan-pick-the-right-bank-to-live-tension-free/"},{"id":"372","question":"Procedure to Avail a Home Loan without Deposit","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/is-home-loan-without-deposit-possible/"},{"id":"373","question":"Process You Need to Know about Gold Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/overview-taking-personal-loan-gold/"},{"id":"374","question":"Purchase approved property from an approved builder","answer":"You have to check whether banks approve the properties of your builder. You also need to understand if a specific project launched by the builder is approved or not. So, you need to check whether the builder and also the entire project including its different phases are approved by the lender or not."},{"id":"375","question":"Questions You Should Ask Your Lender Before Home Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/6-questions-you-should-ask-your-lender-before-home-loan/"},{"id":"376","question":"Reasons Behind Home Loan Rejection","answer":"        Unapproved property or builder or both\n        Defaulted property address being a defaulter\n        Incomplete property and income documents\n        Bad credit history\n        Valuation-related rejection\n        Unstable profession\n        Excessive existing debt\n        Multiple loan rejections"},{"id":"377","question":"Reasons why to Apply for a Personal Loan on WhatsApp","answer":"        Simple & Hassle-free Process\n        Step-by-step Assistance\n        Fastest Approval\n        Easy Comparisons\n        Widest Range of Options are Available"},{"id":"378","question":"Regular Income Generation","answer":"Mutual funds, besides capital appreciation, also fulfill the need of investors looking for a stable flow of income. The debt funds are the ones that you can bet on to generate regular income. These funds invest in bonds, debentures and money-market instruments to fulfill the same. Debt funds have a massive classification of funds, including liquid funds, income funds, bond funds, gilt fund, and much more."},{"id":"379","question":"Regulation","answer":"Mutual fund firms are regulated by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI), the market regulator. As part of the regulation, these firms are mandated to disclose all the details pertaining to the investment to the SEBI. The transparent process helps gain the confidence of the investors.\n"},{"id":"380","question":"Return","answer":"The return potential, particularly in the case of equity funds, is expected to be on the higher side. These funds invest predominantly in the stocks of different companies with distinct market capitalizations. The fund managers also look to widen the portfolio of investors by investing in various sectors of the economy. The capital appreciates on the back of positive cues developing in several sectors like automobile, information & technology, FMCG and others.\n"},{"id":"381","question":"Review your mutual fund investments periodically to balance your portfolio","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/review-mutual-fund-investments-periodically-balance-portfolio/"},{"id":"382","question":"Right time for investment in gilt funds","answer":"You should keep an eye on the factors that can bring down interest rates, cause slowdown in GDP growth, increase inflation, a fall in Index of Industrial Production (IIP), anticipation of a drop in corporate earnings, among others. The right time for investment in gilt funds would be when the interest rates rise and downturn looks all set to grip the economy. Also, you must stay invested for long to get the maximum out of your gilt fund investments."},{"id":"383","question":"Save on Home Loan-Comparison is the Key","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/save-on-home-loan-comparison-is-the-key/"},{"id":"384","question":"SBI Card Prime\n","answer":"With the card comes a welcome e-gift worth ₹3,000 from any of these top brands – Marks and Spencer, Shopper Stop, Yatra,.com, Bata/Hush Puppies and Pantaloons. If you spend ₹50,000 in a calendar quarter, a Pizza Hut e-voucher worth ₹1,000 will also greet you. You can earn 20 reward points for every ₹100 spent on utility bill payments. Spends on the birthdays also attract reward points. You can accumulate as much 20 points for every ₹100 spent on your birthday.\n\nAnnual Fee – ₹2,999 + 18% GST\nWhat’s Special About the Card?\n\nThe e-gift vouchers from top brands, reward points on dining, movies and grocery spends make it one of the exciting reward cards in India. Along with that, there’s a Club Vistara Silver and Priority Pass membership, offering complimentary visits to both domestic and international airport lounges."},{"id":"385","question":"SBI SimplyClick Credit Card","answer":"In addition to 10X reward point offers on spends at specific online food, retail, entertainment and travel brands, there are 5X reward points on other spends at the same time. Besides, Amazon gift card is there to pouch upon at the start. E-voucher worth ₹2,000 can also be given on spends of ₹1 lakh and ₹2 lakh in a year.\n\nAnnual Fee – ₹499 + 18% GST\nWhat’s Special About the Card?\n\nThe 10X reward point offers while spending at renowned online brands like Amazon, Foodpanda and BookMyShow is a big eye-opener for the shoppers. Further, the availability of 5X reward points on all other online spends also makes shoppers go crazy about the card. E-vouchers, fuel surcharge waiver, and the annual fee reversal on spending 1 lakh a year only add to a long list of benefits."},{"id":"386","question":"SBI Student Plus Advantage Card","answer":"        This credit card has been designed solely for the customers who have availed State Bank of India’s education loan. To avail this credit card you need to have a fixed deposit in any branch of SBI. The credit card offers you many privileges like zero annual or renewal fee which is bound to appeal you. No annual fee is charged if you make total purchases of more than Rs. 35,000 in the previous year. You not only earn one reward point for every Rs. 100 you spend but you can use the same reward points to pay off your outstanding balance.\n        You are also entitled to a 2.5% fuel surcharge waiver across all the petrol pumps in India if you buy petrol worth Rs. 500 to Rs. 3,000. Apart from this, you can book railway tickets which will be delivered at your doorstep, pay all your utility bills online and enjoy 10X Reward Points (RP) on all the International spends.\n        You can use the SBI Student Plus Advantage Card in both India and abroad in more than 24 million outlets. You get the provision to transfer the remaining balance of another credit card to your credit card and then get a lower interest rate and pay off the dues in EMIs. This will ensure that you save some money when you pay the credit card dues."},{"id":"387","question":"SBI SWP","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/systematic-withdrawal-plan-sbi-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"388","question":"SBM (State Bank of Mysore) Personal Loan Details","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/sbm-personal-loan/"},{"id":"389","question":"SBP (State Bank of Patiala) Personal Loan Details","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/state-bank-of-patiala-personal-loan/"},{"id":"390","question":"SBP (State Bank of Patiala) Personal Loan EMI Calculator","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/state-bank-of-patiala-personal-loan/"},{"id":"391","question":"SBT (State Bank of Travancore) Personal Loan – EMI Calculator","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/state-bank-of-travancore-personal-loan/"},{"id":"392","question":"SBT (State Bank of Travancore) Personal Loan Online Application\n","answer":"When it comes to applying for a personal loan in State Bank of Travancore, it is absolutely an easy process to apply for the same. Yes, with the help of an online facility, you can send online your loan application form as per your comfort and convenience. Now you don’t have to wait any longer in the queue to submit your loan application. Yes, because with just one click of your mouse you can anytime apply online for this unsecured loan to meet your varied needs."},{"id":"393","question":"Section 24 (Housing Loan Interest Exemption Limit for AY 2016-17)","answer":"You can claim the tax deduction on interest amount paid under Section 24 of the Income Tax Act.\n\nThe maximum tax deduction permissible on interest paid amounts to Rs. 2 lakhs in the case of a self-occupied property.\n\nIncome tax rebate on home loan for an under-construction property is calculated to be 1/5 of the overall interest paid. However, the tax benefit is applicable only when the possession of the property is done.\n\nIn the case of renovation or reconstruction of a home, the maximum amount of tax benefit is reduced to Rs. 30,000."},{"id":"394","question":"Section 80C (Principal Repayment)","answer":"An individual or a Hindu Undivided Family (HUF) paying the principal amount on a home loan can claim tax exemption to a maximum amount of Rs. 1,50,000 as per Section 80C of the IT Act.\n\nYou can avail tax exemption based on the payment regardless of the year in which has taken place. The payment of stamp duty and registration fee are also counted in the tax deduction under the Section 80C even if you have not availed a loan.\n\nTax deduction on principal payment is allowed subsequent to the construction of the house and the issuance of completion certificate.\n\nThe time for which the property is under construction will not fetch you any tax benefits on the principal amount paid.\n\nYou would not be eligible for tax benefits if you transfer the property, on which you have claimed tax exemption under Section 80C, before 5 years from the end of the financial year in which you had taken the possession. The claim amount of tax deduction will be treated as your income in the year when the property is sold and thus you would have to pay tax on the same."},{"id":"395","question":"Section 80ee Income Tax Benefit on Interest Paid on a Home Loan for First Time Buyers","answer":"On both self-occupied and non-self occupied property- Tax deduction is capped to Rs. 1,00,000\n\nHope you have got the answer to the question, is home loan tax deductible? However, there are several conditions that you have to comply with. Wanna know which are those? Check out the points below.\n\nYou can miss out on tax benefits if you are not a borrower despite being an owner of the property. So, sign up for the loan if there are butterflies in your stomach to avail the benefits.\n\nIn case you are a borrower but not an owner of the property, the tax benefits will elude you. So be an owner to claim tax benefits and soothe your pocket against the tax attack.\n\nClaiming of tax benefits will begin from the year in which the property construction is completed."},{"id":"396","question":"Sector Funds","answer":"Funds which invest in a particular sector or industry are known as sector funds. These types of funds offer less diversification and are considered to be risky as they invest in one particular type of sector.\n\n        Sector funds are a part of equity and basically invest in various sectors of the economy like infrastructure, IT, pharmaceuticals, etc.\n        Since the portfolio of these funds focuses investment in one particular type of sector, so the scope for diversification here is limited.\n        They are considered to be risky as they are exposed to a single sector. And, if the sector witnesses a negative sentiment it will adversely impact your MF investment.\n        Normally suitable for an investor with a high- risk appetite."},{"id":"397","question":"Secured Loans for Unemployed","answer":"This is another way unemployed youth in the country can get the secured loan. However, under the same, the individual will have to give some sort of security/asset/collateral to the lender for the sanctioning of the loan. Here, the loan amount will depend directly on the asset value."},{"id":"398","question":"Should One Stop Investments in Mutual Fund SIPs in The Election Year?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/make-mf-sip-investments-in-election-year/"},{"id":"399","question":"SimplySAVE SBI Card","answer":"Simply spend and simply save with this beautifully looking credit card\nAnnual Fee:₹499\n\nPrivileges & Perks\n\n        10X reward points per ₹100 spent on dining, movies, departmental stores and groceries\n        2,000 bonus points on achieving spends of ₹2,000 in the first 60 days\n        Annual fee reversal on spending 90,000 and above in a year\n        1% fuel surcharge waiver across all petrol pumps for transactions between ₹500 – 3,000\n        Earn 1 reward point on every ₹100 that you spend using this card\n        Get ₹100 cashback on your first ATM cash withdrawal\n"},{"id":"400","question":"SIP pause option","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/sip-pause-option-tool-uninterrupted-growth-mf-portfolio/"},{"id":"401","question":"Small Cap Funds","answer":"Funds which diversify their investments in small cap companies are termed as small cap funds. These funds because of their exposure in high beta stocks are positioned on a high risk return trade-off plane compared to large cap funds."},{"id":"402","question":"Standard Chartered Manhattan Platinum Credit Card","answer":"Apart from the cashback you earn spending on groceries at Reliance Fresh, Food Bazaar, Big Bazaar and a few more brick and mortar retailers, you also stand to gain 3X reward points on other spends.\n\nAnnual Fee – ₹999 + 18% GST\nWhat’s Special About the Card?\n\nIt’s a big draw for grocery shoppers with cashback on their spends. The reward points on other spends only add to the card’s popularity. Apart from that, the card has a Good Life Programme which opens the gate of exciting offers on shopping, travel and dining expenses."},{"id":"403","question":"Standard Chartered Platinum Rewards Card","answer":"Get ready to enjoy the best of reward programs with unmatched lifestyle benefits.\n\nAnnual Fee: ₹250 (The fee along with the applicable GST will get reversed upon the first transaction made by a customer within 90 days of the card set-up date)\n\nPrivileges & Perks\n\n        Earn 1000 reward points as an activation offer, equivalent to ₹300 worth on BookMyShow vouchers on 360 rewards\n        Get 5X reward points on fuel, dining and other hotel spends in India\n        Earn 1 reward point on every ₹150 spent on other categories\n        1 reward point equals to ₹0.30\n        Avail 20% cashback on all Uber rides, capped to ₹600 in a month. However, for this to avail,\n        the total monthly spends in a calendar month have to be more than ₹15,000"},{"id":"404","question":"Standard Chartered Super Value Titanium Card","answer":"The 5% cashback on fuel spends can save on vehicle refill, telephone and utility payments. You can earn a maximum cashback of ₹200 per month and ₹100 per transaction. However, to get the cashback credited on your account, it’s important to make a minimum transaction of ₹750. To add to the benefits is the 1 reward point offer for every ₹150 spent on other expenses.\n\nAnnual Fee – ₹750 + 18% GST\nWhat’s Special About the Card?\n\nAll in all, a good pick considering the cashback and reward offers on several spends such as vehicle refill, telephone, utility. What adds to the weight of this card is the 5X reward points for overseas point-of-sales (POS) spends and a complimentary access to more than 1,000 airport lounges worldwide for premium banking customers. There’s a Good Life Programme which makes it easy to access exciting discount offers on dining, travel and other spends."},{"id":"405","question":"State Bank of Bikaner and Jaipur Personal (SBBJ) Loan EMI Calculator","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/state-bank-of-bikaner-and-jaipur-personal-loan/"},{"id":"406","question":"State Bank of Mysore (SBM) Personal Loan EMI Calculator ","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/sbm-personal-loan/"},{"id":"407","question":"State Bank of Patiala Personal (SBP) Loan Interest Rates","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/state-bank-of-patiala-personal-loan/"},{"id":"408","question":"State Bank of Travancore (SBT) Personal Loan ","answer":"Looking for funds and want to fulfill your wishes? Well, look no further as State Bank of Travancore is here with its Personal Loan product that has a perfect combination of low-interest rates and higher loan amount. Whatever be the purpose or occasion, SBT is ready with attractive personal loan offers to let that happen in the nicest way possible. Be it your marriage, education, abroad traveling, business expansion or anything, you can get a customized loan offer. This loan comes with an attractive rate of interest, low processing fee, flexible repayment options, and other alluring features."},{"id":"409","question":"steps /guide to get most out of your SIP investment","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/step-step-guide-get-sip-investment/"},{"id":"410","question":"Steps to Apply for a Personal Loan on WhatsApp","answer":"Step 1: Give a missed call to 8130633535 (You will receive a message on your WhatsApp)\n\nStep 2: Answer the questions asked by the chatbot\n\nStep 3: Provide your full name, email ID and Date of birth\n\nStep 4: Mention your monthly income, occupation & residence city\n\nStep 5: Provide your company name\n\nStep 6: Enter the required loan amount"},{"id":"411","question":"Steps to Apply for Credit Cards on WhatsApp\n","answer":"just follow a few simple steps described below and embark into a world where rewards, privileges and conveniences are up for grabs.\n\n        Visit the official website of Wishfin\n        Go to ‘Credit Cards’ section\n        Click on Apply with the Ease of WhatsApp Chat\n        Enter your mobile number and then click on ‘CONTINUE WITH WHATSAPP’ at the bottom\n        Subsequently, a 2-member WhatsApp group, involving you and Wishfin, would be formed regarding credit card application\n        You would then need to answer some personal and profession related questions\n        Submit your application\n        And you are Done!"},{"id":"412","question":"Steps to Apply for Home Loan on WhatsApp","answer":"The procedure is very simple and quick. You just have to follow the below steps:\n\n        Give a missed call to 9555103000 (You will receive a message on your WhatsApp)\n        Answer the questions asked by the chatbot\n        Provide your full name, email ID and Date of birth\n        Mention your monthly income and residence city\n        Provide your required loan amount\n        Enter the value of the property\n\nOnce you complete the process, you get the list of options where you are eligible for a home loan. You will get options with the bank name, interest rate, EMI, tenure and eligible loan amount. To know more about home loans, visit Wishfin."},{"id":"413","question":"Steps to Check CIBIL Score Free on WhatsApp","answer":"Wishfin gives you the first ever chance to check your CIBIL score through WhatsApp. Inda's first process to check CIBIL completly on WhatsApp is now possible. You just have to follow the steps mentioned below:\n\n        Give a missed call to +91-8287151151\n        Mobile Number will be added to WhatsApp Chat\n        Mention your Name, Date of Birth & Gender\n        Enter your PAN Number\n        Provide your complete residence address\n        Enter your Email ID\n\nAs you soon as you complete the above process, you will get your latest CIBIL Score in your WhatsApp chat box. The other way to get your CIBIL score via WhatsApp is to fill up the form and the link, through which you can check the score, will be sent to your mobile number. You can login to your account using CIBIL login details and get detailed CIBIL report free for one year."},{"id":"414","question":"Steps to Start an SIP (Systematic Investment Plan) through WhatsApp","answer":"        Enter your mobile number in the form.\n        You will receive a message from Wishfin Mutual Fund on your WhatsApp\n        Accept the Terms and conditions mentioned in the chat to proceed\n        Enter your Permanent Account Number (PAN)\n        Select your financial goal through SIP investment\n        Mention the monthly SIP amount.\n        Select one fund from the list of recommended funds\n        Choose your SIP start date\n        Provide your personal details such as full name as per PAN card, mother’s name, gender, date of birth and full residence address.\n        Mention your email ID.\n        Mention your annual income in lakhs and your profession.\n        Share your bank account details (Bank Name, IFSC code, Account number) for automatic SIP deduction\n        Confirm the submitted details."},{"id":"415","question":"Strong Financial Future with SIPs, This Onam","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/know-net-asset-value-mutual-fund-calculation/"},{"id":"416","question":"Systematic Investment Plan (SIP)","answer":"Investing your money is among the most important decisions. Yet, mutual fund investment through Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) is the most preferred type of investment because of the convenient investment option."},{"id":"417","question":"Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) ","answer":"\tSystematic Investment Plan (SIP) is a mechanism by which you can invest in mutual fund schemes. As per the SIP, an individual is required to pay a fixed amount be it monthly, quarterly or annually for a certain time period.\n\nSIP is envisaged to convert small investment into a big one over a period of time. As the amount is constant and invested regularly, you get extra units in the declining market and lesser units when the value remains high. SIP helps you deal with the market uncertainties and thus proves to be an affordable option for the investors."},{"id":"418","question":"Systematic Investment Plan in Mutual Fund","answer":"SIP is a disciplined form of investment where the investor invests a fixed amount of money at a regular interval. It is a suitable option for small and individual investors. The features of investing through SIP are as follows:\n\n        It channelizes and encourages regular investment\n        It can be started with the amount as low as ₹500\n        It is a smart financial planning tool that helps to build a corpus over time\n        SIP offers the benefit of rupee cost averaging\n        The deduction is automatically made from the account on the selected date post activation of SIP"},{"id":"419","question":"Systematic Withdrawal Plan from SBI Mutual Fund ","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/systematic-withdrawal-plan-sbi-mutual-fund/"},{"id":"420","question":"Tab Capital Personal Loan","answer":"Tab Capital Pvt. Ltd. Company provides a personal loan to the professionals and the salaried individuals to meet their personal expenses. The company extends a loan up to ₹50 lacs and for the flexible tenure of 7 years. These unsecured loans can be paid before the tenure ends at the zero percent pre- payment charges."},{"id":"421","question":"Tab Capital Personal Loan Details ","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/tab-capital-personal-loan/"},{"id":"422","question":"Tab Capital Personal Loan EMI Calculator","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/tab-capital-personal-loan/"},{"id":"423","question":"Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited Personal Loan","answer":"Are you looking to buy a new household appliance? Is there a marriage at home? Or want to travel to your favorite destination? Well, whatever the case may be, with Personal Loan everything is possible because it makes things possible for you. Yes, with the help of Personal Loan all your wishes can easily be fulfilled. This is the reason that Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited has come to the picture to serve your personal needs with ease. So, if you want to enjoy a life with your wishes fulfiled, a personal loan from Tamilnad Mercantile Bank is the call of the day."},{"id":"424","question":"Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited Personal Loan Details","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-limited-personal-loan/"},{"id":"425","question":"Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Limited Personal Loan EMI Calculator","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-limited-personal-loan/"},{"id":"426","question":"Tax Benefits","answer":"Equity Linked Savings Scheme (ELSS), a part of equity mutual fund, lets the investors avail tax deduction on their investment for upto ₹1.5 lakh in a financial year. The tax deductions can be claimed under Section 80C of the Income Tax Act. ELSS, though, comes with a lock-in-period of 3 years."},{"id":"427","question":"Tax Exemption on mortgage loan","answer":"The borrowers get no tax exemption for their mortgage loan. So, if you think that just like a home loan where there is an added advantage for borrowers to get tax exemption u/s 80C & 24(b), there is no such advantage with a loan taken against property."},{"id":"428","question":"Tax Rates","answer":"Long-term debt mutual funds qualify for indexation benefits. For capital gain on investments held over a year, tax rate could either be 10% without indexation and 20% with indexation. Tax rate on long-term capital gain on property, gold remains 20% with the indexation of cost."},{"id":"429","question":"Tax-saver Bank Fixed Deposit","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/compare-elss-and-other-tax-saving-schemes/"},{"id":"430","question":"Taxation in Gold ETFs","answer":"Treated as mutual funds, Gold ETFs are taxed on the basis of non-equity mutual fund norms. Gold ETF investors will have to pay tax subsequent to the redemption of the units. However, tax redemption here is similar to the taxation rules applicable for the physical gold."},{"id":"431","question":"tell me about yourself","answer":""},{"id":"432","question":"Tenure of the mortgage loan","answer":"The maximum tenure available for a loan against the mortgage of the property is 15 years. You can choose a tenure for the loan between 1 year to 15 years or less."},{"id":"433","question":"the 10 Commandments of a Home Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/10-commandments-of-home-loan/"},{"id":"434","question":"the factors that encourage investments in equity mutual funds","answer":"Higher Returns – The investments made in equity mutual funds have delivered an average of 15-18% returns for investors in a 10-year horizon. Such returns can help beat the inflationary pressures and allow you to fulfill your financial goals.\n\nLarge Cap Funds – These funds invest the money predominantly in stocks of top 100 companies according to the market capitalization.\n\nMulti-cap Funds – These funds invest across the market capitalization to ensure greater diversification of the investor capital.\n\nMid-cap Funds – These funds invest the corpus predominantly in stocks of top 101 to 250 companies according to the market capitalization.\n\nSmall-cap Funds -These funds invest the money in stocks of companies that are ranked after the top 250 entities according to the market capitalization.\n\nTax Efficient – Lump sum investments made in equity mutual funds offer tax benefits to the investors. Capital gains up to ₹1 lakh arising out of the sale of equity MF units after 3 years would be free of tax. Capital gains above 1 lakh are taxed at 10%. Even if you sell within 1-3 years, gains above 1 lakh would be taxed at the same 10%. However, if you sell before a year, 15% tax would be charged."},{"id":"435","question":"the mistakes that you should avoid while applying for personal loan.","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/avoid-mistakes-hassle-free-personal-loan-journey/"},{"id":"436","question":"the right tool to build strong investment portfolio","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/ulip-mutual-fund-choose-right-tool-build-strong-investment-portfolio/"},{"id":"437","question":"The secret to creating wealth with your salary hike","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/secret-to-creating-wealth-with-your-salary-hike-is-here/"},{"id":"438","question":"These Credit Cards with Best Accelerated Reward Points","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-with-accelerated-reward-points/"},{"id":"439","question":"These Top Dining Credit Cards Are Every Foodie’s Delight","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-for-dining-india/"},{"id":"440","question":"Things to Consider in Mutual Fund Offer Documents","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/know-look-mutual-fund-offer-document/"},{"id":"441","question":"Things to keep in mind before choosing FMP","answer":"        Keep an eye on the appropriate tenure of the FMP along with their liquidity needs\n        Know tax implications with a firm focus on indexation benefits\n        Check the reputation of the fund house where you are about to invest\n        Underlying investments must be made in quality debt instruments\n"},{"id":"442","question":"Things to Remember While Choosing a Home Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/things-to-remember-while-choosing-a-home-loan/"},{"id":"443","question":"This Investment Can Get You Higher Returns on Your Bonus","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/lump-sum-bonus-investment/"},{"id":"444","question":"Tips for investors looking for joyful ride with mutual fund investment","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/things-keep-mind-investing-mutual-funds/"},{"id":"445","question":"Tips for Prospective Borrowers","answer":"The tips suggested above were for customers who are already servicing personal loans. For those who are yet to avail this loan, they must compare the different interest rates before choosing the one that lowers the repayment burden. They can gauge the effect of interest rates by checking the personal loan EMI calculator, which sums up the repayment in a few seconds. The calculator is available online to make it easy for you. Just enter the loan amount, interest rate and tenure tenure in the calculator, which will then show the EMI and interest outgo over the course of a loan."},{"id":"446","question":"Top 5 banks for Home Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/home-loans/home-loan-pick-the-right-bank-to-live-tension-free/"},{"id":"447","question":"Top 5 Best Travel Credit Cards With No Annual Fee","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-travel-credit-cards-with-no-annual-fees/"},{"id":"448","question":"Top 6 Best Credit Cards with Low Annual Fee","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-with-low-annual-fees/"},{"id":"449","question":"Top 6 Best Credit Cards with Low Annual Fee","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-with-low-annual-fees/"},{"id":"450","question":"Top 7 Best Credit Cards for Movie Lovers","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-for-movie-lovers/"},{"id":"451","question":"Top Cashback & Reward Credit Cards in India","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-cashback-reward-credit-cards-india/"},{"id":"452","question":"Top Selling Credit Cards in India","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/top-selling-credit-cards/"},{"id":"453","question":"Top Travel Credit Cards in India","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-travel-credit-cards-in-india/"},{"id":"454","question":"Top-performing Small Cap Funds","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/invested-small-cap-funds-fetched-return-50-3-years/"},{"id":"455","question":"Tops Banks for WhatsApp Personal Loan Application","answer":"Here is a list of banks available on WhatsApp to apply for a personal loan\n\n        HDFC Bank\n        ICICI Bank\n        Standard Chartered Bank\n        Kotak Mahindra Bank\n        Fullerton India Bank\n        Bajaj Finserv\n        RBL Bank\n        IndusInd Bank\n        Yes Bank\n        DCB Bank\n        Capital First"},{"id":"456","question":"Traditional mode of payment","answer":"Under this mode of payment plan you are required to pay 10% to 15% of the purchase price when you book your property, another 80% to 90% within a given time-frame. The remaining amount you can pay within 45 to 60 days. The remaining amount of the cost of the property include stamp duty, registration fee and other legal charges. The major risk with these kinds of property is delay in construction and delivery of the property. At times, you receive a property with some changes, which was not similar to the project shown at the time of booking. Delayed in the construction also increase the price of property you have booked. In such cases, you are bound to pay the increased price of the property.\n\nTo avoid such issues builders have come up with different options of making payment. They offer you free period for payment till you will get possession. Even some ask you to pay EMIs once you get the possession of your home. These are some easy way out to lure the customers to buy property."},{"id":"457","question":"Types of balanced fund\n","answer":"Equity Balanced Fund\n\nThe asset allocation in this type of fund is predominantly towards equity, in the range of 70%-75%. The rest of the investment is efficiently allocated within the debt instruments. With the equity balanced fund, you enjoy the higher returns of equity and also get compensated for any shortfall in the earning through the regular flow of income emanating from debt instruments.\n\nDebt Balanced Fund\n\nDebt balanced fund ensures investment safety as well as offers returns from the capital market."},{"id":"458","question":"Types of Loan.","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"459","question":"Ultra Short-Term Debt Funds","answer":"These are the funds which invest in fixed-income instruments and are mostly liquid having short-term maturities. If you wish to park your cash for a shorter tenure, these funds are for you.\n\n        Another category of debt funds, ultra short-term debt funds (also called liquid-plus funds) are a perfect tool for the investors to put their money in fixed income schemes.\n        These funds mainly invest in highly liquid, fixed income securities with short-term maturities ranging from 6 Months to 1 Year.\n        These funds help investors avoid interest rate risks. Despite this, they are riskier and can fall prey to market fluctuations."},{"id":"460","question":"Union Bank of India Personal Loan","answer":"Being one of the largest government-owned banks of India, founded in Mumbai, Union Bank of India is a name to reckon with.  The Head Office building of the Bank in Mumbai was inaugurated by Mahatma Gandhi, and his prescient words on that occasion anticipated the tremendous progress of the Bank that it enjoys throughout the following decades.With a huge network of 4,129 ATMs spread across every nook and corner of the country, this bank with its various products caters the needs of all. Amidst its list of products, Union Bank Personal Loan plays a vital role in fulfilling the personal needs of all."},{"id":"461","question":"Union Bank of India Personal Loan Details","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/union-bank-india-personal-loan/"},{"id":"462","question":"Union Bank of India Personal Loan EMI Calculator","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/union-bank-india-personal-loan/"},{"id":"463","question":"Unique Features of Home Loan Application through WhatsApp","answer":"The world is on the internet or WhatsApp (metaphorically) and when a long procedure to get a home loan is here, it is nothing less than a wish come true. Read below the benefits of applying for housing loans through WhatsApp:\n\n        First ever home loan through WhatsApp\n        Process is as simple as chatting with your friends\n        Can be done anytime anywhere (literally)\n        Long list of options on your WhatsApp chat box.\n        No charges for this application process."},{"id":"464","question":"Unit Linked Insurance Plan (ULIP)","answer":"A Unit Linked Insurance Plan (ULIP) offers insurance and investment to investors under a single integrated plan. Under ULIP, a portion of the premium paid by you is used to offer insurance cover while the rest gets invested in several equity and debt schemes. Insurers collect the money from you to build a pool of fund to invest in both equity and debt instruments in different proportions. As a ULIP policy holder, you will be allotted units, the net asset value (NAV) of which gets determined on a  daily basis. The NAV decides the rate of returns that you will get from the ULIP policy. But you must know the charges before hand to put you on the safe path. "},{"id":"465","question":"Use mutual fund to plan your retirement in the smartest way possible","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/use-mutual-fund-plan-retirement-smartest-way-possible/"},{"id":"466","question":"Useful Tips for the Speedy Approval of Personal Loan","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/useful-tips-speedy-approval-personal-loan/"},{"id":"467","question":"Vintage Financial Solutions Personal Loan","answer":"Vintage Credit & Leasing Pvt. Ltd. company offers a personal loan to all the salaried individuals living in Delhi/ NCR region. The loan amount can be used for any purpose as the company doesn’t restrict the usage of funds disbursed. The loans offered by the company are sanctioned up to ₹15,00,0000 for the period of 12 – 24 months to meet the urgent fund requirement.The loans are provided without any security or guarantor. The collateral free loan can be repaid in easy installments and can be paid before the expiration date at the penal rate of 2%."},{"id":"468","question":"Vintage Financial Solutions Personal Loan Details","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/vintage-financial-solutions-personal-loan/"},{"id":"469","question":"Vintage Financial Solutions Personal Loan EMI Calculator ","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/vintage-financial-solutions-personal-loan/"},{"id":"470","question":"Want to Earn Regular Income?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/top-performing-income-funds/"},{"id":"471","question":"Want to Get Higher Returns on Your Investment?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/want-get-higher-returns-investment-choose-mid-cap-funds/"},{"id":"472","question":"Want to Invest in NFOs? Bet on these Upcoming MF Offers","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/want-invest-nfos/"},{"id":"473","question":"What are the benefits of having a good CIBIL Score?","answer":"However, it does not mean that if you have a bad CIBIL score, you can not get a loan or a credit card. Many people get loans and also use credit cards even if they have 0 or bad CIBIL score. But - beggars are not choosers. There are surely some advantages of being on the good side of the scale. So, here are some of the benefits of maintaining a good credit score.\n\n1. Increases eligibility for loans - CIBIL score is the numeric representation of payment history. If you have a good credit score, the lender will be interested in giving a loan to you.\n2. Gives access to best Credit Cards - Some of the great credit cards require a specific credit score which will be accessible to you only if you have a good credit or CIBIL score.\n3. Authenticity for a lower rate of interest - Especially in the case of loans, those having a positive payment history and credit score are more likely to get a lower rate on loans in addition to their present repayment capacity.\n4.  To build a credit history - Just in case, you have zero credit history and score, the moment you start using a credit card or paying EMIs, your credit history will build up and so will your credit score. This will make you eligible for better options in the future."},{"id":"474","question":"What are the best credit cards for students in India?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/best-credit-cards/best-credit-cards-for-students-india/"},{"id":"475","question":"What are the Factors that Affect Personal Loan Tenure","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/factors-affecting-personal-loan-tenure/"},{"id":"476","question":"What are the Risks and Rewards of Mutual Fund Investment?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/risks-and-rewards-of-mutual-fund-investment/"},{"id":"477","question":"What are the Types of Mutual Funds?","answer":"        1 Equity Funds\n            1.1 ELSS (Equity Linked Savings Scheme)\n            1.2 Large Cap Funds\n            1.3 Mid Cap Funds\n            1.4 Small Cap Funds\n            1.5 Multi-Cap Funds\n            1.6 Sector Funds\n            1.7 Global Funds\n        2 Debt Funds\n            2.1 Ultra Short-Term Debt Funds\n            2.2 Gilt Funds\n            2.3 Bond Fund\n            2.4 Liquid Funds\n        3 Balanced Funds (Hybrid Funds)\n            3.1 Income Funds\n            3.2 Capital Protection Fund\n            3.3 Fund of Funds\n        4 Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs)\n            4.1 Index Funds\n            4.2 Gold ETFs"},{"id":"478","question":"What are These Insta Loans on Credit Card All About?","answer":"Well, they are nothing but a pre-approved loan on your unutilized credit card limit. The loan amount to be offered will be blocked against the credit limit left. So, you need to check your eligibility for the same."},{"id":"479","question":"what are you doing?","answer":""},{"id":"480","question":"what are your thoughts  over me","answer":""},{"id":"481","question":"what can you do?","answer":"I can help you in making better financial decisions/"},{"id":"482","question":"What can you use a Personal Loan for?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/what-can-you-use-a-personal-loan-for/"},{"id":"483","question":"What can you use a Personal Loan for?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/what-can-you-use-a-personal-loan-for/"},{"id":"484","question":"What do you mean by Loan?","answer":"Loan is a thing that is borrowed, especially a sum of money that is expected to be paid back with interest. Do you want some? [yes,No]"},{"id":"485","question":"What do you need for Gold ETFs?","answer":"You are required to open a demat and trading account with a stock exchange broker in order to invest in Gold ETFs."},{"id":"486","question":"What do you need to get home loan approval","answer":"        Approved property purchase from an approved builder\n        Proper documents (both income and property)\n        Good credit history\n        Elaborate your liquid assets to gain lender’s trust\n        Save money for down payment\n        Building long term relationship with the lender\n        Guarantor\n        Professional stability\n        Few existing commitments (financial)"},{"id":"487","question":"What does NAV reflect?","answer":"The NAV symbolises the liquidation value of your investments and helps find out the performance of the mutual fund by keeping a track of the same. With NAV, you can keep a close eye of the fluctuations of the market affecting the performance of the mutual fund that you would have opted for. NAV also helps investors to calculate their returns as well as manage monthly payments in advance. NAV not only helps you know your returns and risks, but also helps spot the mutual funds worth the investments you make.\n\nKey points to remember\n\n        NAV of a mutual fund is calculated by the mutual fund or various accounting firms engaged for the task\n        NAV is generally declared after the closing hours of the exchange as mutual funds are dependent upon the movement in stock markets\n        As per the norms of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI), it is mandatory for mutual funds to publish their NAVs on every business day\n        NAV is computed assets minus the expense ratio of a fund. The expense ratio is the summation of all the annual expenses of the mutual fund. These expenses include operating costs, management fees, transfer agent fees, distribution and marketing fees, audit fees and custodian fees."},{"id":"488","question":"What Exactly NFO (New Fund Offers) is?","answer":"Asset management companies (AMCs) launch NFO from time to time. The NFO allows you to buy mutual fund units at Rs 10 per unit, which is usually charged during the subscription period. In case of a close-ended fund, you can purchase the units only at the time of subscription. Further, you have to hold the units till the time the subscription is valid. However, in case of an open-ended fund, you can buy units even after the expiry of subscription period and redeem the same any time."},{"id":"489","question":"What is a CIBIL/Credit report?","answer":"CIBIL report is a single unified document that contains credit history across different lenders over a significant period of time. It is a comprehensive report that provides details of an individual’s or corporate entity’s borrowing history and repayment record. The CIBIL report includes the following information:\n\n        Personal details of an applicant (name, age, gender and address)\n        Employment details and earnings\n        Number of hard enquiries made by potential lenders on receipt of the loan/credit card application\n        Record of previous and current loans along with the payment record\n        Any defaults on loan\n        The details of settled loans, if any\n        Total credit limit and the amount spent monthly (Credit Utilisation Ratio)\n        Any credit card payment defaults\n        Credit score\n\nThis report provides lenders the detailed information of the applicant’s creditworthiness on the basis of previous and current credit behaviour. Based on the report,lenders take the lending decision.\n\n"},{"id":"490","question":"What is Loan?","answer":"Loan is a thing that is borrowed, especially a sum of money that is expected to be paid back with interest. Do you want some? [yes,No]"},{"id":"491","question":"What is my CIBIL Score?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/cibil-score"},{"id":"492","question":"what is SBBJ Personal (State Bank of Bikaner and Jaipur) Loan?","answer":"Live your life with peace and harmony as State Bank of Bikaner and Jaipur is here with Personal Loan. Yes, no matter what your financial are, such as medical expenses, credit card debt, home renovation or travelling to your favourite destination, SBBJ caters to all your personal needs by fulfilling all your dreams. You can avail loan to fulfill any of your personal requirements, be it the education of your child or purchasing new furnitures or fixtures."},{"id":"493","question":"what is SBM (State Bank of Mysore) Personal Loan?","answer":"Have you ever thought of the stuff that can fulfill all your wishes? As far as wishes are concerned, they have no boundaries as the imagination power is infinite. You could dream of flying all the way to exotic locations around the world or riding on a jaw-dropping car or studying in top universities. All that can be fulfilled via a personal loan from State Bank of Mysore (SBM), a Bangalore-headquartered public lender with close to 1,000 branches across the country to serve you. At SBM, a personal loan is available to get wishes, like a wedding, medical emergency, debt consolidation or traveling to some foreign location, fulfilled. Even though you have to repay it, the attractive interest rates do not pinch your pocket much. So, the stage is set to embark on a wonderful phase of your life with SBM Personal Loan."},{"id":"494","question":"What is State Bank of Patiala Personal (SBP) Loan?","answer":"Founded in 1917, State Bank of Patiala with its wide range of products and services, is known for catering the needs of all. As far as personal loans are concerned, State Bank of Patiala has all that a  borrower needs. Yes, no matter what your desires are, the loan scheme of SBP bank never leaves you disappointed. Be it the renovation of your house, buying your dream car or travelling to your favourite destination, SBP is with you to fulfill all your personal wishes with a loan.\n\nState Bank of Patiala (SBP) offers personal loans with attractive rate of interest and higher loan amount facility, making the lender as one of the best personal loan providers in India."},{"id":"495","question":"What is the processing fee on top-up?","answer":"A processing fee on a normal home loan is applicable on the top-up as well. So, it will also be variable from one lender to another. The fee generally ranges from 0.35% to 1% of the disbursed loan amount."},{"id":"496","question":"what is the weather ","answer":"I do not know please search it on internet."},{"id":"497","question":"what is your  function","answer":"I am wishchat, AI based bot of wishfin. I help people take \nbetter financial decisions and live a properous life."},{"id":"498","question":"what is your name","answer":""},{"id":"499","question":"what kind of loans can i get from wishfin ?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"500","question":"What kind of Loans can i get?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"501","question":"what kind of loans do wishfin provide?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"502","question":"what kind of loans do you provide?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"503","question":"What Made Wishfin to Come with WhatsApp Application for Credit Cards?","answer":"Technology is fast changing the world we live in. The paperwork of the 20th Century made way to the fast-paced Internet era in the 21st Century. But technology, as we speak of, never stops evolving. The invention of WhatsApp, a few years ago, is a prime example of people adopting the latest changes doing the rounds. Now as we are living in the world of WhatsApp, Wishfin won’t have chosen a better platform than this to let customers experience the madness and thrill that credit cards bring to the fore."},{"id":"504","question":"What Personal Loan Tenure  Stands For?","answer":"Personal loan tenure is nothing, but the duration for which you borrow the money from banks/lenders. Moreover, the minimum repayment period is 1 year/12 months, and the maximum is 5 years/60 months given by various banks or lenders. More to the point, when it comes to personal loan tenure, there are many factors that create an effect here.Personal loan tenure is nothing, but the duration for which you borrow the money from banks/lenders. Moreover, the minimum repayment period is 1 year/12 months, and the maximum is 5 years/60 months given by various banks or lenders. More to the point, when it comes to personal loan tenure, there are many factors that create an effect here."},{"id":"505","question":"What to look for in an investment?","answer":"        Know your purpose\n        Do simple investments\n        Take expert advice\n        Invest 15-20% of your income\n        Follow the Diversification strategy\n        Don’t be emotional\n        Watch the fees\n        Have patience"},{"id":"506","question":"what types of loan can i get from wishfin ?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"507","question":"what types of loan can i get?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"508","question":"what types of loan do wishfin provide?","answer":"Wishfin provides three kind of loans: [Personal,Home,Car] "},{"id":"509","question":"When do people normally sell mutual fund?","answer":"        nvestors normally look to sell mutual funds that start to under perform\n        Investors look to maximise profits by selling mutual funds that start delivering exceptional performances\n        Sometimes the stagnancy in the fund performance compels investors to sell the mutual fund and invest the proceeds in other investment forms.\nFrom the points stated above, it is observed that investors pay heeds to the performance factor only when they look to sell the mutual fund. But it may not prove fruitful if you sell the mutual fund purely on performance only as there are other factors also that you must consider. First, know when you can think of selling the mutual fund."},{"id":"510","question":"When is the right time to invest in SIP?","answer":"We have a good news for you, there is no such thing as the perfect age or the ideal time to start saving for your future. The sooner you start, the better return you will get. There is no age criteria for SIP investment because all you need to have is the KYC documents and a bank account. So, irrespective of the type of funds, if you start at a young age and maintain a disciplined investment pattern, the returns can be amazing.\n"},{"id":"511","question":"When is the right time to sell mutual fund?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/mutual-fund-sell-puzzle-know-not/"},{"id":"512","question":"Where should you invest in SIP?","answer":"Even though there are no restrictions when it comes to choosing the best mutual fund, it is always advisable to do a proper research and put your money at a place that can give you a higher return in a long run. You can start with debt funds as they act as emergency funds and can be withdrawn easily. After 2-3 years, you can switch to equity funds especially if you are planning for long-term investment."},{"id":"513","question":"Where To Get A Personal Loan?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/where-to-get-a-personal-loan/"},{"id":"514","question":"Where to invest for good returns for post-retirement life?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/mutual-fund/best-mutual-funds-retired-people/"},{"id":"515","question":"Who can apply for a Home Loan Top-Up?","answer":"An existing home loan borrower who has continuously paid EMI may apply for a top-up at the present lender. However, even new customers who transfer their home loan to a new lender. So, you can check at your lender if you are eligible for a top-up or you can transfer your loan to another lender to get the benefit."},{"id":"516","question":"Who can invest in FMPs (Fixed Maturity Plans)?","answer":"        FMPs are ideally suited for risk averse investors who want to churn out fixed income from the market\n        Investors whose area of investment comes at par with the tenure of FMP\n        Investors seeking enhanced return after tax by taking indexation benefit\n        Investors seeking less volatility in their returns"},{"id":"517","question":"who is your father?","answer":"I am a chatbot. Some AI and ML enthusiastic people made me\nand now i growing with the help of data."},{"id":"518","question":"who made you","answer":"I am a chatbot. Some AI and ML enthusiastic people made \nme and now i growing with the help of data."},{"id":"519","question":"Who should invest in CPOS ( Capital Protection debt funds) ?","answer":"        CPOS is perfectly suited for investors looking to protect their invested capital against the downside risk while participating in the equity market to enjoy higher returns at the same time.\n        As capital protection-oriented schemes are close-ended funds with a fixed maturity period of 1-5 years, it is imperative you invest in the same with a long-term investment horizon. These funds are a good option during volatile markets with medium to low levels of inflation.\n        These funds are designed for investors with a defined financial goal."},{"id":"520","question":"Why do NFOs Come in Bull-run?","answer":"AMCs invariably launch NFOs to tap into the psyche of investors who think prudent to invest when markets are at a higher level and the investment cost is lower. So, when investors see NFOs being priced at a cheaper rate of Rs 10 per unit in a growing market, they pump in a large sum of money with a view to generate more return. And to capitalize on this investor mindset, mutual fund firms come up with NFO and enhance their asset under management (AUM)."},{"id":"521","question":"Why Fixed Maturity Plans (FMPs)?","answer":"Volatility Management– As FMPs purchase securities with a fixed maturity date, you will be immune from the interest rate risk upon holding the instrument till the maturity.\n\nTax Efficiency– With FMP, you can get the advantage of indexation that adjusts the purchase price of FMPs for inflation so that you are taxed on actual returns (Maturity Value-Indexed Cost).\n\nDiversification- FMP investment means purchasing various securities such as fixed deposits, recurring deposits. Dispersing the money across such securities cut down the risk factor."},{"id":"522","question":"Why invest in Mutual Fund SIP?","answer":"As the name suggests, this is a systematic way towards investment and starts with as low as ₹500 which is within the reach of the masses. A systematic platform like SIP (Systematic Investment Plan) is a great option to start multiplying your money. Let us suppose you have just started your professional life and are looking for the best place to invest. Where will you invest? The decision, of course, lies in your hands and depends on the factors that are important for an investor."},{"id":"523","question":"Why Investing in mutual fund is a good option for retirement?","answer":"Mutual funds are more flexible investment products which do not have any restriction on payment. You can withdraw in between without any penalty. Depending on your risk appetite, you can choose various mutual fund schemes."},{"id":"524","question":"Why Should You Avoid the Trap of Fixed Rate on Home Loans?","answer":"Yes, it’s a fact that the home loan interest rate remains the same when you get the loan on a fixed basis. The principal and interest portion of the EMI remains the same throughout and so can instill confidence in you. But the rate of interest can always be a couple of percentages higher opposed to floating home loans. Now, you can get the fixed rate loan either for a full loan term or for some years."},{"id":"525","question":"Why you should avail a credit card loan?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/credit-card/why-avail-credit-card-loan/"},{"id":"526","question":"Why you should not opt personal loan for home renovation?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/not-opt-personal-loan-home-renovation/"},{"id":"527","question":"Will a bank give me a Personal Loan ?","answer":"https://www.wishfin.com/personal-loans/will-bank-give-personal-loan/"},{"id":"528","question":"Will checking CIBIL multiple times hamper overall credit score?","answer":"No, you can check your CIBIL score at Wishfin as per your will without making a dent in your overall credit worthiness. If otherwise you go and apply for loans directly at bank or NBFC then the score can fluctuate a bit."},{"id":"529","question":"wishfin, can i afford to take loan?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"530","question":"Wishfin, Can I borrow some money from you?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"531","question":"wishfin, Can you lend me loan?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"532","question":"wishfin, Can you lend me some money?","answer":"What kind of loan do you want? Please, select from the given options: [Travelling Loan,Home Loan,Car Loan,Child's Future Loan]"},{"id":"533","question":"would you marry me?","answer":"I do not believe in marriage"},{"id":"534","question":"would you wanna go on a date with me ?","answer":"awwww, I wish I can but am already engaged with my dataset."},{"id":"535","question":"you are idiot","answer":"// what did it make to describe this you about me"},{"id":"536","question":"you are of no use","answer":"language please."},{"id":"537","question":"you are very smart","answer":"thank you for such kind words."}]